Wow/O ,/O what/O a/O crowd/O ./O 
Thank/O you/O very/O much/O everybody/O ./O 
Such/O an/O honor/O ./O 
With/O the/O snow/O coming/O down/O and/O it/O 's/O a/O little/O cold/O outside/O and/O you/O have/O hundreds/O of/O people/O still/O outside/O trying/O to/O get/O in/O ./O 
But/O you/O know/O ,/O we/O wo/O n't/O wait/O ./O 
We/O 'll/O go/O ahead/O ./O 
Right/O ?/O 
We/O 'll/O go/O ahead/O ./O 
First/O of/O all/O ,/O congratulations/O to/O the/O Iowa/ORGANIZATION State/ORGANIZATION basketball/O team/O ./O 
You/O had/O a/O --/O what/O was/O that/O all/O about/O ?/O 
I/O turned/O on/O the/O game/O ./O 
I/O said/O ,/O ``/O Wow/O ,/O this/O should/O n't/O be/O that/O good/O of/O a/O game/O ./O ''/O 
And/O at/O the/O end/O of/O the/O game/O ,/O I/O said/O ,/O ``/O Who/O won/O ?/O ''/O 
Yes/O ?/O 
That/O was/O great/O and/O it/O 's/O a/O great/O achievement/O ./O 
I/O also/O want/O to/O pay/O my/O respects/O to/O Ben/PERSON Carson/PERSON ./O 
They/O had/O a/O really/O bad/O accident/O ./O 
Some/O of/O his/O staffers/O were/O hurt/O really/O bad/O ./O 
So/O I/O just/O want/O to/O pay/O my/O respects/O to/O Ben/PERSON ./O 
He/O 's/O a/O good/O guy/O --/O a/O really/O good/O guy/O --/O and/O his/O staffers/O and/O hopefully/O they/O get/O better/O ./O 
Say/O a/O prayer/O for/O them/O ./O 
Okay/O ?/O 
We/O 've/O had/O an/O amazing/O time/O today/O ./O 
We/O 've/O been/O all/O over/O Iowa/LOCATION and/O we/O 're/O going/O to/O be/O here/O tomorrow/O ./O 
We/O 're/O going/O to/O be/O here/O so/O much/O you/O 're/O going/O to/O get/O so/O sick/O of/O me/O ./O 
You/O 're/O going/O to/O say/O ,/O ``/O Please/O ,/O tell/O him/O to/O get/O out/O of/O here/O ./O 
Tell/O him/O to/O leave/O ./O 
Tell/O him/O to/O go/O ./O ''/O 
But/O we/O 've/O had/O an/O incredible/O time/O ./O 
And/O you/O know/O it/O started/O really/O --/O we/O 've/O had/O really/O a/O pretty/O good/O week/O ./O 
The/O debate/O last/O week/O --/O everybody/O watched/O the/O debate/O ./O 
And/O who/O knew/O about/O these/O debates/O ?/O 
I/O did/O n't/O know/O anything/O about/O the/O debates/O ./O 
And/O it/O 's/O been/O fun/O and/O it/O 's/O been/O interesting/O ./O 
And/O I/O 've/O been/O treated/O semi-fairly/O by/O the/O moderators/O ./O 
Not/O 100/O %/O ./O 
Some/O have/O been/O very/O fair/O actually/O ,/O and/O some/O have/O been/O not/O so/O fair/O ./O 
And/O you/O know/O ,/O a/O lot/O of/O the/O press/O has/O n't/O been/O very/O fair/O ./O 
Boy/O ,/O look/O at/O the/O press/O back/O there/O ./O 
They/O must/O think/O there/O 's/O a/O big/O event/O going/O happen/O today/O ./O 
Wow/O ,/O that/O 's/O a/O lot/O of/O them/O --/O it/O 's/O like/O the/O Academy/O Awards/O ./O 
But/O we/O 've/O had/O an/O amazing/O --/O it/O 's/O been/O an/O amazing/O experience/O and/O it/O started/O really/O on/O June/O 16th/O when/O we/O came/O down/O the/O escalator/O ./O 
We/O came/O down/O that/O escalator/O and/O it/O was/O --/O I/O said/O ,/O ``/O Let/O 's/O go/O ''/O to/O my/O wife/O ,/O who/O 's/O been/O so/O supportive/O and/O so/O wonderful/O ./O 
I/O said/O ,/O ``/O Let/O 's/O go/O ./O 
We/O 're/O going/O to/O make/O America/LOCATION great/O again/O ./O 
That/O 's/O what/O we/O 're/O going/O to/O do/O ./O ''/O 
And/O you/O know/O ,/O it/O 's/O hard/O to/O do/O this/O because/O when/O you/O think/O of/O it/O I/O 've/O never/O done/O it/O before/O ./O 
I/O 've/O never/O been/O a/O politician/O ./O 
Thank/O goodness/O but/O I/O 've/O never/O been/O a/O politician/O ./O 
I/O 've/O always/O done/O jobs/O and/O put/O a/O lot/O of/O people/O to/O work/O ./O 
Tens/O of/O thousands/O of/O people/O over/O the/O years/O ./O 
And/O you/O know/O ,/O I/O have/O thousands/O of/O Hispanics/O that/O love/O me/O ./O 
The/O Nevada/LOCATION poll/O just/O came/O out/O where/O I/O 'm/O leading/O with/O Hispanics/O ,/O which/O I/O knew/O ,/O I/O knew/O ./O 
And/O we/O came/O out/O at/O that/O particular/O opening/O when/O I/O opened/O and/O said/O I/O 'm/O going/O to/O run/O for/O president/O I/O gave/O up/O a/O lot/O ./O 
You/O know/O ,/O gave/O up/O a/O lot/O of/O different/O things/O including/O telling/O our/O friends/O at/O NBC/ORGANIZATION no/O more/O Apprentice/O ./O 
That/O 's/O hard/O to/O do/O ./O 
You/O have/O a/O top/O show/O and/O you/O say/O ,/O ``/O I/O 'm/O not/O doing/O it/O anymore/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O sorry/O ./O ''/O 
They/O wanted/O to/O do/O it/O so/O badly/O ./O 
And/O Steve/PERSON Burke/PERSON ,/O who/O 's/O a/O fantastic/O executive/O ,/O came/O up/O to/O my/O office/O and/O said/O ``/O Come/O on/O ,/O Donald/PERSON ./O 
Come/O on/O ./O 
Do/O it/O ./O 
You/O 're/O not/O going/O to/O run/O ./O 
Do/O it/O ./O 
Do/O it/O ./O ''/O 
I/O said/O ,/O ``/O Steve/PERSON ,/O I/O 'm/O going/O to/O run/O ./O ''/O 
I/O was/O pretty/O sure/O ./O 
You/O know/O ,/O that/O was/O about/O two/O months/O before/O ./O 
I/O was/O pretty/O sure/O ./O 
It/O really/O is/O a/O tough/O thing/O to/O do/O ./O 
You/O know/O ,/O all/O my/O life/O I/O 've/O heard/O ``/O If/O you/O 're/O a/O very/O successful/O person/O ,/O you/O 'll/O never/O run/O for/O president/O ./O 
You/O 'll/O never/O really/O run/O for/O politics/O ./O 
But/O you/O 'll/O never/O ever/O run/O for/O president/O ./O ''/O 
And/O I/O built/O a/O great/O company/O and/O it/O 's/O a/O tremendous/O number/O ./O 
You/O saw/O the/O filings/O ./O 
The/O press/O was/O going/O to/O look/O so/O closely/O ./O 
It/O was/O like/O D-Day/O when/O we/O put/O those/O papers/O in/O ./O 
You/O know/O ,/O first/O thing/O I/O did/O I/O announced/O ./O 
They/O said/O ,/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O he/O 's/O actually/O going/O to/O do/O it/O ''/O because/O most/O of/O them/O said/O ``/O He/O 'll/O never/O do/O it/O ./O ''/O 
Then/O when/O I/O signed/O .../O that/O 's/O when/O you/O sign/O your/O life/O away/O ./O 
And/O I/O signed/O that/O ./O 
They/O said/O ,/O ``/O Whoa/O !/O 
He/O signed/O that/O ./O 
Well/O ,/O he/O 'll/O never/O file/O his/O financials/O because/O maybe/O he/O 's/O not/O as/O rich/O as/O everybody/O thinks/O ./O ''/O 
And/O I/O filed/O the/O financials/O and/O they/O saw/O an/O unbelievable/O --/O you/O did/O n't/O hear/O a/O thing/O about/O it/O ./O 
Oh/O boy/O ,/O were/O they/O looking/O ./O 
I/O mean/O ,/O were/O they/O looking/O ./O 
And/O almost/O 100/O pages/O ./O 
The/O biggest/O report/O ever/O filed/O with/O the/O FEC/ORGANIZATION in/O terms/O of/O that/O ./O 
And/O it/O showed/O a/O company/O that/O 's/O a/O phenomenal/O company/O with/O some/O of/O the/O great/O assets/O ,/O very/O little/O debt/O ,/O tremendous/O cash/O flow/O ./O 
You/O know/O ,/O the/O way/O it/O 's/O supposed/O to/O be/O ./O 
And/O it/O 's/O great/O ./O 
And/O the/O reason/O I/O tell/O you/O that/O is/O because/O that/O is/O the/O kind/O of/O thinking/O we/O need/O now/O in/O the/O United/LOCATION States/LOCATION ./O 
We/O need/O that/O kind/O of/O thinking/O ./O 
We/O need/O that/O --/O whatever/O it/O is/O ./O 
We/O need/O a/O mentality/O that/O 's/O going/O to/O --/O you/O know/O ,/O we/O 're/O at/O $/O 19/O trillion/O in/O debt/O ./O 
It/O 's/O going/O to/O be/O up/O to/O $/O 21/O trillion/O ./O 
You/O saw/O that/O horrible/O budget/O ./O 
Horrible/O ,/O horrible/O budget/O that/O was/O approved/O two/O weeks/O ago/O and/O that/O 's/O going/O to/O lift/O it/O ./O 
And/O so/O we/O went/O along/O and/O a/O lot/O of/O things/O have/O happened/O and/O then/O the/O polls/O came/O out/O which/O I/O love/O and/O new/O ones/O came/O out/O today/O and/O I/O 'll/O tell/O you/O right/O now/O ./O 
You/O know/O ,/O now/O that/O we/O 're/O at/O it/O ./O 
And/O they/O came/O out/O some/O brand/O new/O ones/O --/O some/O beauties/O ./O 
And/O one/O 's/O coming/O out/O --/O I/O guess/O a/O big/O one/O 's/O coming/O out/O ./O 
I/O do/O n't/O know/O exactly/O what/O it/O is/O but/O it/O 's/O got/O to/O be/O pretty/O good/O because/O I/O see/O the/O response/O ./O 
I/O mean/O ,/O even/O this/O with/O all/O the/O people/O still/O trying/O to/O come/O into/O this/O building/O ./O 
Somebody/O said/O it/O 's/O a/O barn/O ./O 
This/O is/O a/O very/O nice/O barn/O actually/O ./O 
But/O with/O all/O of/O the/O people/O still/O trying/O to/O come/O in/O ,/O you/O see/O what/O it/O is/O ./O 
And/O we/O do/O have/O something/O special/O in/O a/O couple/O of/O minutes/O ./O 
To/O me/O ,/O it/O 's/O really/O special/O because/O it/O 's/O a/O person/O that/O I/O think/O is/O a/O spectacular/O person/O ./O 
So/O it/O 's/O very/O special/O to/O me/O ./O 
But/O then/O the/O polls/O came/O out/O and/O some/O of/O them/O --/O as/O an/O example/O --/O national/O polls/O 38/O %/O for/O Trump/ORGANIZATION ,/O 20/O %/O for/O second/O ./O 
I/O would/O n't/O even/O names/O ./O 
Right/O ?/O 
I/O wo/O n't/O even/O mention/O names/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O going/O to/O be/O non/O -/O confrontational/O today/O for/O a/O change/O ./O 
21/O %/O for/O the/O second/O ./O 
11/O %/O ./O 
And/O then/O they/O 're/O all/O down/O ./O 
Some/O of/O them/O are/O actually/O at/O 0/O %/O and/O 1/O %/O ./O 
I/O do/O n't/O know/O ./O 
Jeb/O --/O well/O ,/O you/O know/O ,/O Jeb/PERSON 's/O got/O one/O problem/O ./O 
He/O loves/O Common/O Core/O ,/O meaning/O he/O wants/O your/O kids/O educated/O from/O Washington/LOCATION ,/O which/O is/O immediately/O no/O good/O ./O 
And/O his/O second/O problem/O is/O he/O 's/O very/O weak/O on/O illegal/O immigration/O ./O 
Remember/O ,/O he/O said/O they/O come/O as/O an/O act/O of/O love/O ./O 
I/O said/O ,/O ``/O What/O ?/O 
They/O come/O as/O an/O act/O of/O love/O ?/O ''/O 
So/O I/O think/O those/O are/O two/O very/O bad/O points/O frankly/O ./O 
.../O So/O South/LOCATION Carolina/LOCATION just/O came/O out/O and/O that/O 's/O 32/O %/O for/O Trump/PERSON ,/O 18/O %/O for/O second/O ,/O 11/O %/O for/O third/O ./O 
Great/O ./O 
Florida/LOCATION leading/O by/O a/O lot/O --/O 31/O %/O ,/O 19/O %/O ,/O 13/O %/O ,/O and/O then/O all/O down/O in/O the/O dumps/O ./O 
Georgia/LOCATION just/O came/O out/O ./O 
I/O have/O 33/O %/O ./O 
Yeah/O ,/O do/O n't/O forget/O that/O 's/O 33/O %/O ./O 
Hard/O to/O believe/O ./O 
That/O 's/O with/O 14/O people/O ,/O 15/O people/O ./O 
I/O do/O n't/O know/O when/O they/O took/O it/O but/O it/O was/O recent/O ./O 
33/O %/O ./O 
Connecticut/LOCATION --/O now/O ,/O Tom/PERSON Brady/PERSON loves/O me/O and/O that/O 's/O sort/O of/O like/O ,/O you/O know/O ,/O and/O I/O love/O Tom/PERSON Brady/PERSON by/O the/O way/O ./O 
35/O %/O to/O 18/O %/O to/O 9/O %/O to/O 2/O %/O ./O 
You/O know/O ,/O to/O nothing/O ./O 
Maryland/LOCATION just/O came/O out/O ./O 
Maryland/LOCATION --/O great/O place/O --/O 32/O %/O to/O 15/O %/O to/O 11/O %/O to/O 9/O %/O and/O then/O you/O know/O they/O sort/O of/O phase/O out/O ./O 
You/O ever/O hear/O of/O a/O place/O called/O Iowa/LOCATION ?/O 
Oh/O ,/O I/O love/O this/O ./O 
We/O 're/O doing/O actually/O great/O ./O 
First/O of/O all/O ,/O I/O have/O to/O tell/O you/O ./O 
You/O know/O ,/O they/O never/O report/O it/O ./O 
Even/O CNN/ORGANIZATION does/O n't/O report/O it/O ./O 
CNN/ORGANIZATION does/O a/O poll/O ,/O probably/O spent/O millions/O ,/O they/O never/O report/O their/O poll/O ./O 
The/O CNN/ORGANIZATION poll/O was/O 33/O %/O for/O Trump/PERSON ,/O 20/O %/O for/O Chris/PERSON ./O 
Nobody/O talks/O about/O it/O ./O 
Nobody/O talks/O about/O it/O ./O 
They/O do/O n't/O talk/O about/O it/O ./O 
They/O talk/O about/O --/O CNN/ORGANIZATION is/O reporting/O other/O people/O 's/O polls/O ./O 
So/O ,/O I/O call/O up/O ./O 
I/O say/O ,/O ``/O Wait/O a/O minute/O ./O 
You/O 're/O CNN/ORGANIZATION ./O 
You/O spent/O a/O fortune/O on/O polls/O and/O you/O do/O n't/O report/O your/O own/O polls/O because/O I/O 'm/O winning/O by/O a/O lot/O ./O ''/O 
And/O they/O have/O no/O excuse/O but/O they/O keep/O reporting/O other/O polls/O ./O 
But/O we/O 're/O doing/O well/O ./O 
I/O think/O we/O 're/O doing/O a/O lot/O better/O than/O anyone/O knows/O ./O 
Gravis/O just/O came/O out/O --/O 34/O %/O for/O Trump/PERSON ,/O 28/O %/O for/O Cruz/PERSON ./O 
PPP/ORGANIZATION 28/O %/O for/O Trump/PERSON ,/O 26/O %/O for/O Cruz/PERSON ./O 
In/O other/O words/O ,/O it/O 's/O a/O little/O close/O here/O ./O 
Quinnipiac/ORGANIZATION poll/O --/O very/O respected/O 31/O %/O for/O Trump/ORGANIZATION ,/O 29/O %/O for/O Cruz/PERSON ./O 
And/O then/O again/O CNN/ORGANIZATION 33/O %/O to/O 20/O %/O ./O 
So/O we/O 're/O --/O I/O think/O we/O 're/O doing/O good/O ./O 
I/O think/O we/O 're/O actually/O doing/O better/O than/O the/O polls/O ./O 
Now/O ,/O I/O could/O do/O this/O ./O 
I/O could/O say/O ,/O ``/O Well/O ,/O I/O just/O want/O to/O do/O well/O in/O Iowa/LOCATION ./O ''/O 
I/O want/O to/O win/O Iowa/LOCATION ,/O folks/O ./O 
Because/O look/O ,/O I/O love/O the/O people/O ./O 
The/O evangelicals/O have/O been/O phenomenal/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O doing/O great/O with/O the/O evangelicals/O but/O nationwide/O I/O 'm/O winning/O with/O evangelical/O --/O I/O do/O n't/O know/O if/O you/O know/O that/O --/O by/O a/O lot/O nationwide/O ./O 
With/O Iowa/LOCATION ,/O I/O 'm/O doing/O really/O well/O with/O the/O evangelicals/O ./O 
We/O 're/O doing/O really/O well/O with/O the/O Tea/ORGANIZATION Party/ORGANIZATION ./O 
We/O 're/O doing/O well/O --/O I/O mean/O ,/O you/O hear/O the/O numbers/O ./O 
I/O mean/O ,/O these/O are/O the/O numbers/O ./O 
But/O I/O actually/O think/O we/O 're/O doing/O even/O better/O than/O the/O polls/O ./O 
And/O you/O know/O ,/O there/O 's/O the/O thing/O that/O a/O lot/O of/O people/O said/O ,/O you/O know/O ,/O they/O call/O up/O ,/O ``/O Are/O you/O going/O to/O vote/O for/O Trump/PERSON ?/O 
He/O 's/O got/O very/O ,/O very/O tough/O immigration/O policies/O ./O 
He/O wants/O to/O destroy/O Obamacare/O and/O replace/O it/O with/O something/O a/O lot/O better/O ./O ''/O 
I/O 'm/O going/O to/O do/O that/O ./O 
Okay/O ?/O 
But/O you/O know/O ,/O a/O lot/O of/O people/O ,/O they/O 'll/O pick/O up/O the/O phone/O and/O they/O 'll/O hear/O different/O things/O and/O they/O 'll/O say/O ,/O ``/O Uh/O ,/O no/O I/O 'll/O vote/O for/O --/O ``/O and/O then/O they/O 'd/O get/O in/O the/O booth/O and/O they/O say/O ,/O ``/O Trump/PERSON is/O my/O man/O ./O ''/O 
There/O are/O a/O lot/O of/O people/O saying/O that/O we/O 're/O going/O to/O do/O a/O lot/O better/O ./O 
But/O we/O 'll/O see/O because/O Feb./O 1st/O you/O have/O to/O get/O to/O caucus/O ,/O you/O have/O to/O go/O out/O ./O 
You/O 've/O got/O to/O do/O it/O ./O 
Otherwise/O ,/O we/O 've/O all/O wasted/O our/O time/O ./O 
You/O know/O ,/O one/O of/O the/O groups/O in/O Maine/LOCATION and/O it/O was/O like/O incredible/O ./O 
We/O were/O in/O different/O places/O up/O in/O New/LOCATION England/LOCATION recently/O and/O New/LOCATION Hampshire/LOCATION was/O amazing/O ./O 
And/O the/O people/O are/O standing/O there/O ./O 
It/O was/O so/O cold/O ./O 
There/O was/O one/O little/O group/O of/O --/O despite/O global/O warming/O --/O you/O know/O ,/O you/O hear/O about/O ``/O It/O was/O so/O cold/O ./O ''/O 
It/O was/O windchill/O below/O zero/O ./O 
And/O people/O were/O standing/O outside/O for/O hours/O trying/O to/O get/O in/O ./O 
And/O then/O you/O hear/O the/O announcers/O ./O 
``/O Well/O ,/O will/O they/O show/O up/O to/O vote/O ?/O ''/O 
And/O I/O do/O n't/O know/O much/O but/O I/O say/O like/O if/O people/O are/O going/O to/O stand/O out/O for/O four/O hours/O in/O the/O cold/O or/O the/O heat/O because/O believe/O me/O they/O stood/O out/O in/O the/O heat/O during/O the/O summer/O and/O during/O the/O fall/O like/O you/O would/O n't/O believe/O in/O Tennessee/LOCATION ,/O in/O Texas/LOCATION where/O we/O had/O 21,000/O people/O ,/O no/O matter/O where/O we/O go/O we/O have/O these/O big/O crowds/O but/O they/O 'll/O stand/O for/O hours/O and/O hours/O to/O get/O in/O ./O 
Why/O are/O n't/O they/O going/O to/O go/O and/O vote/O ?/O 
Or/O in/O your/O case/O caucus/O ?/O 
Why/O are/O n't/O they/O going/O to/O go/O and/O vote/O ?/O 
It/O 's/O sort/O of/O an/O amazing/O thing/O ./O 
So/O we/O think/O they/O 're/O going/O to/O really/O be/O --/O why/O would/O somebody/O wait/O for/O hours/O for/O four/O hours/O and/O not/O going/O to/O take/O two/O minutes/O to/O vote/O ?/O 
Now/O ,/O yours/O is/O a/O little/O more/O complicated/O because/O the/O caucus/O system/O is/O a/O little/O bit/O different/O ./O 
It/O 's/O a/O very/O interesting/O system/O ./O 
But/O it/O is/O different/O ./O 
Here/O 's/O what/O I/O have/O to/O say/O about/O Iowa/LOCATION ./O 
It/O 's/O very/O important/O ./O 
So/O you/O know/O there/O 's/O a/O movement/O to/O move/O Iowa/LOCATION to/O the/O back/O of/O the/O pack/O ./O 
Okay/O ?/O 
You/O know/O that/O ./O 
You/O 'll/O still/O see/O me/O but/O you/O wo/O n't/O see/O other/O people/O ./O 
Believe/O me/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O loyal/O ./O 
To/O a/O fault/O I/O 'm/O loyal/O ./O 
But/O you/O 're/O going/O to/O see/O ./O 
I/O give/O you/O my/O word/O ./O 
I/O win/O ;/O they/O 're/O not/O touching/O Iowa/LOCATION ./O 
This/O is/O an/O amazing/O tradition/O ./O 
No/O ,/O seriously/O ./O 
This/O is/O an/O amazing/O tradition/O ./O 
They/O 're/O not/O moving/O Iowa/LOCATION back/O ./O 
And/O they/O 're/O not/O moving/O New/ORGANIZATION Hampshire/ORGANIZATION either/O because/O they/O 're/O talking/O about/O Iowa/LOCATION ,/O New/LOCATION Hampshire/LOCATION ./O 
They/O 're/O not/O touching/O New/LOCATION Hampshire/LOCATION ./O 
So/O ,/O we/O 're/O going/O to/O just/O keep/O it/O the/O way/O it/O is/O ./O 
It/O really/O is/O ./O 
It/O 's/O an/O amazing/O ./O 
First/O of/O all/O ,/O you/O 're/O amazing/O people/O ./O 
But/O all/O over/O the/O country/O it/O 's/O a/O movement/O all/O over/O the/O country/O ./O 
The/O people/O are/O incredible/O ./O 
They/O want/O to/O make/O America/LOCATION great/O again/O ./O 
They/O 're/O going/O to/O do/O something/O that/O 's/O special/O ./O 
And/O you/O know/O we/O used/O to/O talk/O silent/O majority/O ?/O 
I/O say/O it/O 's/O the/O noisy/O majority/O because/O it/O 's/O actually/O a/O noisy/O majority/O ./O 
It/O 's/O not/O a/O silent/O majority/O ./O 
But/O people/O are/O fed/O up/O ./O 
So/O I/O started/O on/O June/O 16th/O and/O we/O did/O well/O ./O 
Practically/O from/O the/O beginning/O we/O went/O up/O ./O 
And/O if/O you/O remember/O ,/O we/O started/O at/O nothing/O ./O 
You/O know/O ,/O we/O started/O at/O nothing/O because/O nobody/O believed/O I/O was/O going/O to/O -LSB-/O run/O -RSB-/O ./O 
Even/O when/O they/O --/O my/O wife/O said/O ,/O ``/O You/O know/O if/O you/O run/O ,/O you/O 're/O going/O to/O win/O ./O ''/O 
I/O said/O ,/O ``/O What/O do/O you/O mean/O ?/O ''/O 
She/O said/O ,/O ``/O People/O do/O n't/O believe/O you/O 're/O going/O to/O run/O ./O ''/O 
At/O the/O polls/O ./O 
I/O was/O getting/O these/O little/O polls/O ./O 
I/O felt/O like/O some/O of/O these/O guys/O now/O that/O are/O senators/O and/O governors/O ;/O they/O get/O these/O little/O polls/O ./O 
.../O Jeb/PERSON again/O ,/O right/O ?/O 
Boy/O ,/O he/O 's/O taking/O a/O lot/O of/O abuse/O ./O 
You/O know/O ?/O 
I/O told/O him/O ``/O You/O know/O what/O ?/O 
You/O should/O use/O the/O name/O Bush/PERSON ./O 
What/O 's/O wrong/O ?/O 
Use/O the/O name/O Bush/PERSON ./O 
I/O mean/O ,/O maybe/O it/O 's/O not/O working/O but/O it/O 's/O better/O than/O Jeb/PERSON right/O ?/O ''/O 
You/O know/O ,/O I/O really/O do/O ./O 
Get/O rid/O of/O the/O exclamation/O point/O and/O just/O put/O Jeb/PERSON Bush/PERSON ./O 
It/O 's/O your/O name/O ./O 
Do/O n't/O be/O ashamed/O of/O your/O name/O ./O 
So/O anyways/O ,/O I/O wish/O him/O the/O best/O ./O 
But/O ,/O you/O know/O ,/O I/O started/O and/O I/O started/O at/O like/O 2/O %/O or/O 3/O %/O and/O then/O it/O went/O to/O 6/O %/O and/O then/O it/O went/O to/O 9/O %/O ./O 
And/O each/O time/O the/O pundits/O --/O these/O real/O geniuses/O back/O here/O --/O some/O of/O them/O are/O sitting/O back/O here/O --/O these/O real/O geniuses/O like/O George/PERSON Will/PERSON with/O the/O little/O glasses/O --/O take/O away/O the/O glasses/O ./O 
He/O looks/O like/O a/O dumb/O guy/O ,/O I/O 'm/O telling/O you/O ./O 
But/O each/O time/O these/O geniuses/O would/O say/O ,/O ``/O Well/O ,/O he/O 's/O reached/O his/O plateau/O ./O 
He/O 's/O plateaued/O ''/O at/O 6/O %/O ,/O right/O ?/O 
Then/O it/O goes/O to/O 11/O %/O ./O 
``/O Well/O ,/O you/O know/O ,/O this/O is/O surprising/O but/O he/O 's/O reached/O his/O plateau/O ./O ''/O 
And/O then/O it/O goes/O to/O 18/O %/O ./O 
And/O then/O it/O went/O to/O 22/O %/O ,/O 24/O %/O ,/O 28/O %/O ,/O then/O it/O went/O to/O 32/O %/O ./O 
Then/O it/O went/O actually/O 42/O %/O in/O the/O Gravis/O poll/O and/O in/O Reuters/ORGANIZATION we/O got/O to/O 42/O %/O and/O even/O a/O little/O above/O that/O ./O 
And/O then/O all/O of/O a/O sudden/O you/O did/O n't/O hear/O so/O much/O about/O the/O plateau/O ./O 
I/O want/O to/O plateau/O at/O 42/O %/O ./O 
You/O know/O ,/O 42/O %/O with/O like/O 14/O people/O that/O 's/O pretty/O good/O ./O 
But/O they/O kept/O saying/O ,/O ``/O He/O 's/O plateaued/O ./O 
That/O 's/O all/O he/O 'll/O get/O ./O 
He/O 's/O got/O these/O followers/O ./O ''/O 
We/O have/O the/O smartest/O followers/O there/O are/O ./O 
Number/O one/O ,/O we/O have/O the/O smartest/O ./O 
And/O the/O hardest/O working/O followers/O ./O 
We/O have/O people/O that/O love/O the/O country/O more/O than/O anybody/O and/O they/O want/O to/O take/O back/O what/O 's/O happened/O because/O our/O country/O is/O going/O to/O hell/O ./O 
We/O can/O be/O nice/O about/O it/O ./O 
We/O can/O say/O it/O nice/O and/O soft/O ./O 
Our/O country/O is/O going/O to/O hell/O ./O 
When/O you/O look/O at/O this/O crazy/O Iran/LOCATION deal/O where/O we/O 're/O paying/O $/O 150/O billion/O and/O they/O give/O us/O the/O five/O back/O but/O they/O do/O n't/O know/O where/O the/O fifth/O is/O and/O you/O understand/O what/O that/O means/O ./O 
That/O 's/O not/O a/O good/O sign/O ./O 
But/O they/O give/O us/O five/O people/O but/O they/O get/O seven/O and/O they/O get/O 14/O off/O the/O Interpol/ORGANIZATION ./O 
These/O are/O bad/O dudes/O ./O 
They/O get/O 14/O plus/O seven/O so/O they/O 're/O getting/O 21/O people/O ./O 
And/O they/O have/O the/O right/O to/O do/O whatever/O they/O want/O from/O an/O enterprise/O standpoint/O ./O 
Right/O to/O do/O oil/O ./O 
Right/O to/O do/O whatever/O they/O want/O ./O 
But/O what/O do/O they/O also/O get/O out/O of/O that/O deal/O ?/O 
First/O of/O all/O ,/O they/O 're/O going/O to/O get/O nuclear/O ./O 
They/O do/O n't/O have/O to/O develop/O nuclear/O missiles/O ./O 
They/O can/O buy/O them/O ./O 
For/O the/O kind/O of/O money/O we/O gave/O them/O ,/O they/O 're/O going/O to/O buy/O them/O ./O 
Why/O are/O they/O going/O to/O develop/O ?/O 
Remember/O the/O deal/O ?/O 
24/O days/O ./O 
They/O have/O 24/O days/O for/O inspection/O period/O ./O 
They/O also/O have/O self-inspection/O ./O 
Right/O ?/O 
But/O we/O paid/O $/O 150/O billion/O ./O 
And/O I/O always/O say/O ,/O ``/O Wow/O ./O 
What/O a/O great/O --/O the/O Persians/O are/O great/O negotiators/O ./O ''/O 
I/O say/O what/O a/O great/O deal/O that/O is/O ./O 
.../O Two/O weeks/O ago/O I/O started/O ./O 
I/O said/O ,/O ``/O Wait/O a/O minute/O ./O 
That/O 's/O not/O a/O good/O deal/O compared/O to/O the/O other/O deal/O ./O ''/O 
They/O took/O over/O Iraq/LOCATION ./O 
We/O gave/O them/O Iraq/LOCATION ./O 
We/O knocked/O the/O hell/O out/O of/O Iraq/LOCATION ./O 
We/O decimated/O their/O armed/O forces/O ./O 
And/O you/O know/O ,/O for/O years/O ,/O they/O would/O fight/O ./O 
For/O many/O ,/O many/O years/O ,/O for/O decades/O they/O 'd/O fight/O ,/O fight/O ,/O fight/O ./O 
Nobody/O would/O win/O ./O 
Fight/O ./O 
They/O 'd/O rest/O ./O 
Then/O they/O 'd/O go/O back/O to/O fight/O ./O 
And/O now/O ,/O we/O gave/O them/O the/O second/O largest/O oil/O reserves/O in/O the/O world/O ,/O which/O is/O Iraq/LOCATION ./O 
We/O gave/O it/O to/O them/O ./O 
Now/O ,/O they/O 're/O going/O into/O Yemen/LOCATION ./O 
And/O if/O you/O look/O at/O Yemen/LOCATION ,/O take/O a/O look/O ./O 
They/O 're/O going/O to/O get/O Syria/LOCATION ./O 
They/O 're/O going/O to/O get/O Yemen/LOCATION ./O 
Unless/O ,/O you/O know/O ,/O trust/O me/O a/O lot/O of/O good/O things/O are/O going/O to/O happen/O if/O I/O get/O in/O ./O 
But/O let/O 's/O just/O sort/O of/O leave/O it/O the/O way/O it/O is/O ./O 
They/O get/O Syria/LOCATION ./O 
They/O get/O Yemen/LOCATION ./O 
Now/O ,/O they/O did/O n't/O want/O Yemen/LOCATION ./O 
But/O did/O you/O ever/O see/O the/O border/O between/O Yemen/LOCATION and/O Saudi/LOCATION Arabia/LOCATION ?/O 
They/O want/O Saudi/LOCATION Arabia/LOCATION ./O 
So/O ,/O what/O are/O they/O going/O to/O have/O ?/O 
They/O 're/O going/O to/O have/O Iraq/LOCATION ./O 
They/O 're/O going/O to/O have/O Iran/LOCATION ./O 
They/O 're/O going/O to/O have/O Iraq/LOCATION ./O 
They/O 're/O going/O to/O have/O Yemen/LOCATION ./O 
They/O 're/O going/O to/O have/O Syria/LOCATION ./O 
They/O 're/O going/O to/O have/O everything/O ./O 
They/O 're/O going/O to/O be/O a/O monster/O ./O 
We/O 've/O created/O this/O ./O 
We/O have/O stupid/O leadership/O ./O 
Really/O stupid/O leadership/O ./O 
So/O when/O I/O started/O ,/O I/O said/O we/O have/O to/O do/O something/O about/O it/O ./O 
It/O 's/O not/O something/O I/O wanted/O to/O do/O ./O 
It/O 's/O something/O we/O have/O to/O do/O ./O 
Because/O I/O 'm/O representing/O you/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O not/O taking/O any/O money/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O not/O ,/O you/O know/O ,/O like/O some/O of/O these/O guys/O where/O they/O 're/O getting/O millions/O and/O millions/O of/O dollars/O from/O people/O I/O know/O and/O they/O 're/O nice/O people/O and/O some/O are/O very/O bad/O people/O but/O they/O have/O no/O interest/O in/O the/O country/O ./O 
They/O have/O interests/O in/O their/O company/O or/O they/O have/O interests/O in/O countries/O they/O 're/O representing/O ./O 
And/O these/O people/O and/O these/O politicians/O are/O going/O to/O do/O exactly/O as/O they/O 're/O told/O by/O their/O lobbyists/O ,/O their/O special/O interests/O ,/O and/O their/O donors/O ./O 
Me/O ,/O I/O 'm/O going/O to/O do/O the/O right/O thing/O ./O 
And/O I/O always/O tell/O the/O story/O ./O 
When/O Ford/ORGANIZATION moves/O to/O Mexico/LOCATION ,/O I/O 'm/O going/O to/O talk/O them/O out/O of/O it/O ./O 
When/O Nabisco/PERSON moves/O its/O plant/O from/O Chicago/LOCATION to/O Mexico/LOCATION ,/O I/O 'm/O going/O to/O talk/O them/O out/O of/O it/O ./O 
Believe/O me/O ./O 
It/O 's/O going/O to/O be/O easy/O ./O 
It/O 's/O going/O to/O be/O easy/O ./O 
So/O ,/O I/O started/O and/O I/O talked/O about/O the/O border/O ./O 
Very/O strong/O on/O immigration/O and/O illegal/O immigration/O ./O 
Took/O a/O lot/O of/O heat/O ./O 
But/O you/O would/O n't/O even/O be/O talking/O about/O that/O subject/O if/O I/O did/O n't/O bring/O it/O up/O ./O 
And/O I/O talked/O about/O again/O I/O talked/O about/O ISIS/ORGANIZATION and/O I/O talked/O about/O ./O 
But/O what/O really/O happened/O is/O after/O Paris/LOCATION we/O had/O 130/O people/O killed/O ./O 
And/O by/O the/O way/O ,/O I/O told/O you/O Common/ORGANIZATION Core/ORGANIZATION is/O dead/O and/O Second/O Amendment/O is/O right/O this/O way/O ./O 
We/O 're/O going/O to/O protect/O the/O Second/O Amendment/O ./O 
We/O 're/O going/O to/O protect/O the/O guns/O ./O 
We/O 're/O going/O to/O protect/O your/O guns/O ./O 
You/O know/O ,/O if/O in/O Paris/LOCATION and/O if/O in/O Los/LOCATION Angeles/LOCATION ,/O we/O had/O the/O two/O maniacs/O that/O were/O married/O ./O 
She/O came/O on/O a/O fiancee/O permit/O .../O You/O know/O ,/O wonderful/O fiancee/O ./O 
She/O was/O totally/O radicalized/O ./O 
Maybe/O radicalized/O him/O ./O 
Maybe/O he/O was/O already/O that/O way/O ./O 
But/O we/O 've/O got/O to/O start/O thinking/O ./O 
We/O have/O to/O start/O using/O our/O head/O ./O 
Bad/O stuff/O is/O happening/O ./O 
We/O have/O to/O find/O out/O what/O 's/O going/O on/O ./O 
We/O have/O a/O president/O who/O wo/O n't/O even/O talk/O about/O the/O term/O ./O 
If/O you/O think/O ,/O he/O wo/O n't/O even/O mention/O anything/O to/O do/O with/O what/O we/O all/O know/O is/O going/O on/O ./O 
And/O you/O ca/O n't/O solve/O the/O problem/O if/O you/O do/O n't/O talk/O about/O it/O ./O 
You/O have/O to/O talk/O about/O it/O ./O 
So/O ,/O very/O ,/O very/O strongly/O we/O started/O talking/O about/O that/O ./O 
And/O then/O after/O Paris/LOCATION --/O and/O by/O the/O way/O ,/O if/O we/O had/O a/O couple/O of/O you/O and/O you/O and/O you/O and/O you/O ,/O if/O we/O had/O three/O or/O four/O people/O in/O that/O room/O in/O Paris/LOCATION as/O an/O example/O where/O they/O have/O the/O toughest/O gun/O laws/O like/O in/O the/O world/O ./O 
You/O ca/O n't/O have/O a/O gun/O unless/O you/O 're/O bad/O guy/O ,/O you/O bought/O a/O gun/O ./O 
And/O they/O walked/O in/O just/O said/O ``/O Boom/O !/O 
Boom/O !/O 
Boom/O !/O 
You/O ,/O move/O over/O ./O 
Boom/O !/O ''/O 
Killed/O 130/O ,/O more/O to/O follow/O because/O there/O are/O people/O that/O are/O so/O badly/O wounded/O ./O 
But/O if/O we/O had/O a/O couple/O of/O --/O few/O of/O the/O people/O that/O I/O pointed/O out/O --/O I/O could/O plenty/O in/O this/O audience/O ,/O believe/O me/O ./O 
But/O if/O they/O had/O guns/O on/O their/O waist/O ,/O if/O they/O had/O guns/O around/O their/O ankle/O where/O the/O bullets/O went/O the/O opposite/O direction/O ,/O it/O would/O have/O been/O a/O whole/O different/O story/O ,/O folks/O ./O 
It/O 'd/O be/O a/O whole/O different/O story/O ./O 
So/O very/O ,/O very/O big/O on/O the/O Second/O Amendment/O ./O 
But/O what/O happened/O is/O all/O of/O a/O sudden/O after/O Paris/LOCATION and/O to/O an/O extent/O ,/O to/O a/O pretty/O big/O extent/O in/O California/LOCATION ,/O what/O happened/O is/O these/O polls/O started/O coming/O in/O where/O everybody/O liked/O Trump/PERSON even/O more/O ./O 
I/O went/O up/O 11/O points/O ./O 
I/O do/O n't/O want/O to/O do/O it/O for/O that/O reason/O ./O 
But/O it/O went/O up/O because/O people/O want/O strength/O just/O like/O having/O the/O family/O of/O John/PERSON Wayne/PERSON ,/O who/O was/O great/O ./O 
I/O love/O John/PERSON Wayne/PERSON ./O 
From/O Iowa/LOCATION ./O 
But/O out/O of/O nowhere/O I/O got/O the/O most/O beautiful/O letter/O from/O his/O daughter/O ,/O who/O you/O just/O met/O ,/O who/O 's/O an/O incredible/O woman/O ,/O and/O she/O said/O ,/O ``/O We/O 'd/O like/O to/O endorse/O you/O ./O ''/O 
John/PERSON Wayne/PERSON was/O a/O strong/O guy/O ./O 
We/O need/O strength/O ./O 
We/O need/O strength/O in/O this/O country/O because/O we/O 're/O withering/O away/O with/O political/O correctness/O nonsense/O ./O 
Okay/O ?/O 
Nonsense/O ./O 
I/O mean/O ,/O if/O you/O think/O of/O it/O ,/O you/O ca/O n't/O say/O ``/O Merry/O Christmas/O ''/O anymore/O ./O 
We/O 're/O going/O to/O say/O ``/O Merry/O Christmas/O ''/O again/O ./O 
You/O go/O into/O these/O department/O stores/O ./O 
They/O do/O n't/O have/O any/O Christmas/O displays/O ./O 
They/O do/O n't/O have/O the/O sign/O ``/O Merry/O Christmas/O ''/O ./O 
Even/O people/O that/O are/O n't/O Christian/O are/O saying/O ``/O Merry/O Christmas/O ./O 
We/O love/O Christmas/O ./O 
Let/O us/O say/O `/O Merry/O Christmas/O '/O ,/O Happy/ORGANIZATION Holidays/ORGANIZATION ./O ''/O 
But/O people/O like/O to/O see/O it/O ./O 
And/O stores/O do/O n't/O put/O it/O up/O anymore/O ./O 
We/O 're/O withering/O away/O ./O 
We/O 're/O going/O in/O the/O wrong/O direction/O ./O 
So/O I/O said/O we/O 're/O going/O to/O do/O this/O and/O I/O had/O no/O idea/O it/O was/O going/O to/O work/O this/O way/O ./O 
I/O figured/O I/O 'd/O be/O in/O the/O pack/O and/O maybe/O like/O a/O race/O horse/O ./O 
You/O know/O ,/O just/O at/O the/O end/O you/O can/O sort/O of/O inch/O it/O out/O ./O 
I/O had/O no/O idea/O to/O have/O 21/O point/O leads/O nationally/O ./O 
We/O 're/O up/O by/O so/O much/O ./O 
And/O you/O know/O ,/O I/O want/O to/O keep/O it/O that/O way/O ./O 
I/O want/O to/O keep/O it/O that/O way/O ./O 
When/O you/O think/O --/O and/O just/O one/O thing/O before/O I/O introduce/O our/O incredible/O person/O ,/O our/O incredible/O guest/O ./O 
But/O one/O thing/O --/O I/O 've/O spent/O to/O this/O point/O almost/O nothing/O and/O I/O 'm/O in/O first/O place/O by/O a/O lot/O ./O 
I/O tell/O this/O story/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O not/O bragging/O about/O spending/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O just/O saying/O I/O 'm/O telling/O the/O story/O ./O 
I/O have/O spent/O --/O they/O 'll/O tell/O you/O --/O almost/O nothing/O and/O I/O 'm/O in/O first/O place/O by/O some/O polls/O have/O me/O 21/O points/O ./O 
That/O 's/O a/O lot/O ./O 
Okay/O ?/O 
You/O know/O some/O people/O have/O 2/O %/O ./O 
I/O have/O a/O lead/O of/O 20/O %/O ./O 
But/O I/O 'm/O in/O first/O place/O by/O a/O lot/O ./O 
Jeb/PERSON has/O spent/O now/O $/O 77/O million/O ./O 
Think/O of/O it/O ./O 
And/O you/O know/O the/O reason/O I/O bring/O him/O up/O --/O I/O would/O n't/O even/O bring/O him/O up/O --/O but/O he/O spends/O a/O fortune/O on/O ads/O against/O me/O ./O 
You/O people/O have/O all/O seen/O it/O before/O I/O got/O along/O with/O everybody/O ./O 
I/O contributed/O to/O everybody/O ./O 
I/O was/O a/O world/O class/O businessman/O ./O 
Now/O I/O 'm/O a/O politician/O ,/O which/O I/O 'd/O hate/O to/O tell/O you/O ./O 
But/O you/O go/O with/O everybody/O ./O 
You/O want/O to/O love/O everybody/O ./O 
You/O want/O them/O all/O to/O love/O you/O unless/O you/O 're/O stupid/O ./O 
But/O you/O want/O everybody/O to/O love/O you/O ./O 
Everybody/O knows/O this/O story/O ./O 
But/O so/O much/O money/O has/O been/O spent/O on/O me/O ./O 
But/O he/O spent/O $/O 79/O million/O ./O 
I/O spend/O nothing/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O in/O first/O by/O a/O lot/O ./O 
He/O 's/O down/O towards/O the/O bottom/O of/O the/O pack/O ./O 
And/O I/O said/O to/O myself/O ,/O ``/O It/O 's/O amazing/O ./O 
Would/O n't/O that/O be/O great/O if/O this/O were/O the/O country/O doing/O this/O ?/O ''/O 
As/O an/O example/O ,/O education/O ./O 
We/O 're/O number/O 28/O in/O the/O world/O ./O 
We/O have/O third/O world/O countries/O that/O are/O ahead/O of/O us/O ./O 
Education/O is/O very/O important/O to/O me/O ./O 
World/O ,/O I/O mean/O ,/O countries/O that/O you/O would/O n't/O believe/O are/O ahead/O of/O us/O ./O 
You/O would/O n't/O believe/O if/O you/O heard/O the/O names/O of/O some/O of/O these/O countries/O ./O 
So/O we/O 're/O 28/O ./O 
But/O we/O 're/O number/O one/O in/O spending/O per/O pupil/O by/O far/O ./O 
Would/O n't/O it/O be/O nice/O if/O you/O had/O like/O this/O election/O process/O where/O we/O spent/O the/O least/O but/O we/O had/O the/O best/O education/O ?/O 
You/O know/O ?/O 
So/O Sweden/LOCATION and/O Norway/LOCATION and/O China/LOCATION and/O others/O are/O the/O best/O ./O 
We/O 're/O nowhere/O near/O them/O and/O yet/O we/O spend/O far/O more/O per/O pupil/O ./O 
So/O we/O 're/O going/O to/O change/O that/O and/O I/O told/O you/O we/O 're/O going/O to/O get/O it/O localized/O but/O we/O 're/O going/O to/O change/O that/O ./O 
Watch/O ,/O you/O just/O watch/O .../O I/O will/O tell/O you/O this/O :/O You/O ca/O n't/O educate/O your/O children/O through/O bureaucrats/O in/O Washington/LOCATION ./O 
And/O that/O 's/O what/O happens/O with/O Common/ORGANIZATION Core/ORGANIZATION ./O 
When/O the/O parents/O take/O over/O and/O I/O really/O mean/O this/O because/O I/O 've/O seen/O it/O ./O 
When/O the/O parents/O surround/O those/O schools/O and/O they/O love/O those/O kids/O and/O they/O love/O those/O pupils/O and/O even/O when/O their/O kids/O graduate/O ,/O they/O are/O committed/O to/O those/O schools/O ,/O they/O 're/O committed/O to/O education/O ./O 
You/O can/O do/O so/O much/O better/O in/O Iowa/LOCATION than/O they/O can/O possibly/O do/O telling/O you/O what/O to/O do/O in/O Washington/LOCATION ./O 
And/O not/O all/O of/O them/O but/O most/O of/O them/O are/O just/O interested/O in/O ``/O Where/O 's/O my/O check/O ?/O 
How/O much/O do/O I/O get/O ?/O 
Let/O 's/O make/O the/O process/O complicated/O ./O ''/O 
And/O some/O of/O the/O things/O that/O your/O kids/O are/O made/O to/O study/O are/O an/O outrage/O ./O 
Okay/O ?/O 
So/O we/O 're/O going/O to/O bring/O that/O back/O locally/O and/O it/O 's/O going/O to/O be/O great/O ./O 
So/O what/O happened/O essentially/O is/O I/O started/O looking/O and/O all/O of/O a/O sudden/O things/O changed/O ./O 
And/O people/O are/O now/O looking/O ./O 
They/O know/O I/O 'll/O do/O great/O with/O China/LOCATION ./O 
I/O 'm/O going/O to/O do/O great/O with/O Japan/LOCATION ./O 
I/O 'm/O going/O to/O do/O great/O with/O Mexico/LOCATION ,/O who/O 's/O killing/O us/O in/O trade/O and/O killing/O us/O also/O at/O the/O border/O ./O 
We/O will/O build/O a/O wall/O and/O you/O know/O who/O 's/O going/O to/O pay/O for/O the/O wall/O --/O Mexico/LOCATION ./O 
They/O 're/O going/O to/O pay/O for/O it/O because/O they/O make/O a/O fortune/O and/O all/O of/O those/O things/O ./O 
But/O now/O ,/O we/O 're/O really/O focused/O on/O security/O and/O I/O 'm/O honored/O because/O I/O will/O tell/O you/O that/O all/O of/O polls/O and/O the/O CNN/ORGANIZATION polls/O where/O said/O in/O particular/O that/O Trump/PERSON is/O just/O not/O by/O a/O little/O bit/O but/O by/O many/O ,/O many/O percentage/O points/O winning/O on/O ISIS/ORGANIZATION ,/O winning/O on/O the/O military/O ,/O winning/O with/O the/O vets/O ./O 
We/O 're/O going/O to/O take/O care/O of/O our/O vets/O big/O league/O ,/O by/O the/O way/O ./O 
Big/O league/O ./O 
Big/O league/O ./O 
And/O we/O 're/O going/O to/O really/O take/O care/O of/O our/O military/O ./O 
It/O 's/O going/O to/O be/O big/O and/O strong/O and/O powerful/O and/O nobody/O 's/O going/O to/O mess/O with/O us/O and/O it/O 's/O the/O cheapest/O thing/O we/O can/O do/O ,/O I/O 'll/O tell/O you/O that/O right/O now/O ./O 
So/O it/O 's/O been/O a/O real/O focus/O ./O 
I/O just/O want/O to/O now/O say/O just/O a/O couple/O of/O words/O about/O a/O very/O special/O person/O ./O 
This/O is/O a/O person/O who/O I/O 've/O known/O for/O a/O long/O time/O ,/O who/O I/O 've/O respected/O for/O so/O long/O ./O 
An/O incredible/O husband/O ./O 
An/O incredible/O family/O ./O 
And/O somebody/O that/O when/O I/O heard/O that/O she/O was/O going/O to/O endorse/O me/O ,/O I/O was/O so/O honored/O ./O 
You/O have/O no/O idea/O how/O honored/O ./O 
And/O I/O would/O like/O to/O bring/O up/O if/O I/O might/O Gov./O Sarah/PERSON Palin/PERSON ./O 
Special/O ,/O special/O person/O ./O 
Thank/O you/O ./O 
Wow/O ./O 
Whoa/O ./O 
That/O is/O some/O group/O of/O people/O ./O 
Thousands/O ./O 
So/O nice/O ,/O thank/O you/O very/O much/O ./O 
That/O 's/O really/O nice/O ./O 
Thank/O you/O ./O 
It/O 's/O great/O to/O be/O at/O Trump/LOCATION Tower/LOCATION ./O 
It/O 's/O great/O to/O be/O in/O a/O wonderful/O city/O ,/O New/LOCATION York/LOCATION ./O 
And/O it/O 's/O an/O honor/O to/O have/O everybody/O here/O ./O 
This/O is/O beyond/O anybody/O 's/O expectations/O ./O 
There/O 's/O been/O no/O crowd/O like/O this/O ./O 
And/O ,/O I/O can/O tell/O ,/O some/O of/O the/O candidates/O ,/O they/O went/O in/O ./O 
They/O did/O n't/O know/O the/O air-conditioner/O did/O n't/O work/O ./O 
They/O sweated/O like/O dogs/O ./O 
They/O did/O n't/O know/O the/O room/O was/O too/O big/O ,/O because/O they/O did/O n't/O have/O anybody/O there/O ./O 
How/O are/O they/O going/O to/O beat/O ISIS/ORGANIZATION ?/O 
I/O do/O n't/O think/O it/O 's/O gon/O na/O happen/O ./O 
Our/O country/O is/O in/O serious/O trouble/O ./O 
We/O do/O n't/O have/O victories/O anymore/O ./O 
We/O used/O to/O have/O victories/O ,/O but/O we/O do/O n't/O have/O them/O ./O 
When/O was/O the/O last/O time/O anybody/O saw/O us/O beating/O ,/O let/O 's/O say/O ,/O China/LOCATION in/O a/O trade/O deal/O ?/O 
They/O kill/O us/O ./O 
I/O beat/O China/LOCATION all/O the/O time/O ./O 
All/O the/O time/O ./O 
When/O did/O we/O beat/O Japan/LOCATION at/O anything/O ?/O 
They/O send/O their/O cars/O over/O by/O the/O millions/O ,/O and/O what/O do/O we/O do/O ?/O 
It/O does/O n't/O exist/O ,/O folks/O ./O 
They/O beat/O us/O all/O the/O time/O ./O 
When/O do/O we/O beat/O Mexico/LOCATION at/O the/O border/O ?/O 
They/O 're/O laughing/O at/O us/O ,/O at/O our/O stupidity/O ./O 
And/O now/O they/O are/O beating/O us/O economically/O ./O 
They/O are/O not/O our/O friend/O ,/O believe/O me/O ./O 
But/O they/O 're/O killing/O us/O economically/O ./O 
The/O U.S./LOCATION has/O become/O a/O dumping/O ground/O for/O everybody/O else/O 's/O problems/O ./O 
Thank/O you/O ./O 
It/O 's/O true/O ,/O and/O these/O are/O the/O best/O and/O the/O finest/O ./O 
When/O Mexico/LOCATION sends/O its/O people/O ,/O they/O 're/O not/O sending/O their/O best/O ./O 
They/O 're/O not/O sending/O you/O ./O 
They/O 're/O not/O sending/O you/O ./O 
They/O 're/O sending/O people/O that/O have/O lots/O of/O problems/O ,/O and/O they/O 're/O bringing/O those/O problems/O with/O us/O ./O 
They/O 're/O bringing/O drugs/O ./O 
They/O 're/O bringing/O crime/O ./O 
They/O 're/O rapists/O ./O 
And/O some/O ,/O I/O assume/O ,/O are/O good/O people/O ./O 
But/O I/O speak/O to/O border/O guards/O and/O they/O tell/O us/O what/O we/O 're/O getting/O ./O 
And/O it/O only/O makes/O common/O sense/O ./O 
It/O only/O makes/O common/O sense/O ./O 
They/O 're/O sending/O us/O not/O the/O right/O people/O ./O 
It/O 's/O coming/O from/O more/O than/O Mexico/LOCATION ./O 
It/O 's/O coming/O from/O all/O over/O South/LOCATION and/O Latin/LOCATION America/LOCATION ,/O and/O it/O 's/O coming/O probably/O --/O probably/O --/O from/O the/O Middle/LOCATION East/LOCATION ./O 
But/O we/O do/O n't/O know/O ./O 
Because/O we/O have/O no/O protection/O and/O we/O have/O no/O competence/O ,/O we/O do/O n't/O know/O what/O 's/O happening/O ./O 
And/O it/O 's/O got/O to/O stop/O and/O it/O 's/O got/O to/O stop/O fast/O ./O 
Islamic/O terrorism/O is/O eating/O up/O large/O portions/O of/O the/O Middle/LOCATION East/LOCATION ./O 
They/O 've/O become/O rich/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O in/O competition/O with/O them/O ./O 
They/O just/O built/O a/O hotel/O in/O Syria/LOCATION ./O 
Can/O you/O believe/O this/O ?/O 
They/O built/O a/O hotel/O ./O 
When/O I/O have/O to/O build/O a/O hotel/O ,/O I/O pay/O interest/O ./O 
They/O do/O n't/O have/O to/O pay/O interest/O ,/O because/O they/O took/O the/O oil/O that/O ,/O when/O we/O left/O Iraq/LOCATION ,/O I/O said/O we/O should/O 've/O taken/O ./O 
So/O now/O ISIS/ORGANIZATION has/O the/O oil/O ,/O and/O what/O they/O do/O n't/O have/O ,/O Iran/LOCATION has/O ./O 
And/O in/O 19/O --/O and/O I/O will/O tell/O you/O this/O ,/O and/O I/O said/O it/O very/O strongly/O ,/O years/O ago/O ,/O I/O said/O --/O and/O I/O love/O the/O military/O ,/O and/O I/O want/O to/O have/O the/O strongest/O military/O that/O we/O 've/O ever/O had/O ,/O and/O we/O need/O it/O more/O now/O than/O ever/O ./O 
But/O I/O said/O ,/O ``/O Do/O n't/O hit/O Iraq/LOCATION ,/O ''/O because/O you/O 're/O going/O to/O totally/O destabilize/O the/O Middle/LOCATION East/LOCATION ./O 
Iran/LOCATION is/O going/O to/O take/O over/O the/O Middle/LOCATION East/LOCATION ,/O Iran/LOCATION and/O somebody/O else/O will/O get/O the/O oil/O ,/O and/O it/O turned/O out/O that/O Iran/LOCATION is/O now/O taking/O over/O Iraq/LOCATION ./O 
Think/O of/O it/O ./O 
Iran/LOCATION is/O taking/O over/O Iraq/LOCATION ,/O and/O they/O 're/O taking/O it/O over/O big/O league/O ./O 
We/O spent/O $/O 2/O trillion/O in/O Iraq/LOCATION ,/O $/O 2/O trillion/O ./O 
We/O lost/O thousands/O of/O lives/O ,/O thousands/O in/O Iraq/LOCATION ./O 
We/O have/O wounded/O soldiers/O ,/O who/O I/O love/O ,/O I/O love/O --/O they/O 're/O great/O --/O all/O over/O the/O place/O ,/O thousands/O and/O thousands/O of/O wounded/O soldiers/O ./O 
And/O we/O have/O nothing/O ./O 
We/O ca/O n't/O even/O go/O there/O ./O 
We/O have/O nothing/O ./O 
And/O every/O time/O we/O give/O Iraq/LOCATION equipment/O ,/O the/O first/O time/O a/O bullet/O goes/O off/O in/O the/O air/O ,/O they/O leave/O it/O ./O 
Last/O week/O ,/O I/O read/O 2,300/O Humvees/O --/O these/O are/O big/O vehicles/O --/O were/O left/O behind/O for/O the/O enemy/O ./O 
2,000/O ?/O 
You/O would/O say/O maybe/O two/O ,/O maybe/O four/O ?/O 
2,300/O sophisticated/O vehicles/O ,/O they/O ran/O ,/O and/O the/O enemy/O took/O them/O ./O 
You/O 're/O right/O ./O 
Last/O quarter/O ,/O it/O was/O just/O announced/O our/O gross/O domestic/O product/O --/O a/O sign/O of/O strength/O ,/O right/O ?/O 
But/O not/O for/O us/O ./O 
It/O was/O below/O zero/O ./O 
Whoever/O heard/O of/O this/O ?/O 
It/O 's/O never/O below/O zero/O ./O 
Our/O labor/O participation/O rate/O was/O the/O worst/O since/O 1978/O ./O 
But/O think/O of/O it/O ,/O GDP/O below/O zero/O ,/O horrible/O labor/O participation/O rate/O ./O 
And/O our/O real/O unemployment/O is/O anywhere/O from/O 18/O to/O 20/O percent/O ./O 
Do/O n't/O believe/O the/O 5.6/O ./O 
Do/O n't/O believe/O it/O ./O 
That/O 's/O right/O ./O 
A/O lot/O of/O people/O up/O there/O ca/O n't/O get/O jobs/O ./O 
They/O ca/O n't/O get/O jobs/O ,/O because/O there/O are/O no/O jobs/O ,/O because/O China/LOCATION has/O our/O jobs/O and/O Mexico/LOCATION has/O our/O jobs/O ./O 
They/O all/O have/O jobs/O ./O 
But/O the/O real/O number/O ,/O the/O real/O number/O is/O anywhere/O from/O 18/O to/O 19/O and/O maybe/O even/O 21/O percent/O ,/O and/O nobody/O talks/O about/O it/O ,/O because/O it/O 's/O a/O statistic/O that/O 's/O full/O of/O nonsense/O ./O 
Our/O enemies/O are/O getting/O stronger/O and/O stronger/O by/O the/O way/O ,/O and/O we/O as/O a/O country/O are/O getting/O weaker/O ./O 
They/O do/O n't/O know/O if/O it/O worked/O ./O 
And/O I/O thought/O it/O was/O horrible/O when/O it/O was/O broadcast/O on/O television/O ,/O because/O boy/O ,/O does/O that/O send/O signals/O to/O Putin/PERSON and/O all/O of/O the/O other/O people/O that/O look/O at/O us/O and/O they/O say/O ,/O ``/O That/O is/O a/O group/O of/O people/O ,/O and/O that/O is/O a/O nation/O that/O truly/O has/O no/O clue/O ./O 
They/O do/O n't/O know/O what/O they/O 're/O doing/O ./O 
They/O do/O n't/O know/O what/O they/O 're/O doing/O ./O ''/O 
We/O have/O a/O disaster/O called/O the/O big/O lie/O :/O Obamacare/O ./O 
Obamacare/O ./O 
Yesterday/O ,/O it/O came/O out/O that/O costs/O are/O going/O for/O people/O up/O 29/O ,/O 39/O ,/O 49/O ,/O and/O even/O 55/O percent/O ,/O and/O deductibles/O are/O through/O the/O roof/O ./O 
You/O have/O to/O be/O hit/O by/O a/O tractor/O ,/O literally/O ,/O a/O tractor/O ,/O to/O use/O it/O ,/O because/O the/O deductibles/O are/O so/O high/O ,/O it/O 's/O virtually/O useless/O ./O 
It/O 's/O virtually/O useless/O ./O 
It/O is/O a/O disaster/O ./O 
And/O remember/O the/O $/O 5/O billion/O Web/O site/O ?/O 
$/O 5/O billion/O we/O spent/O on/O a/O Web/O site/O ,/O and/O to/O this/O day/O it/O does/O n't/O work/O ./O 
A/O $/O 5/O billion/O Web/O site/O ./O 
I/O have/O so/O many/O Web/O sites/O ,/O I/O have/O them/O all/O over/O the/O place/O ./O 
I/O hire/O people/O ,/O they/O do/O a/O Web/O site/O ./O 
It/O costs/O me/O $/O 3/O ./O 
$/O 5/O billion/O Web/O site/O ./O 
Well/O ,/O you/O need/O somebody/O ,/O because/O politicians/O are/O all/O talk/O ,/O no/O action/O ./O 
Nothing/O 's/O gon/O na/O get/O done/O ./O 
They/O will/O not/O bring/O us/O --/O believe/O me/O --/O to/O the/O promised/O land/O ./O 
They/O will/O not/O ./O 
As/O an/O example/O ,/O I/O 've/O been/O on/O the/O circuit/O making/O speeches/O ,/O and/O I/O hear/O my/O fellow/O Republicans/O ./O 
And/O they/O 're/O wonderful/O people/O ./O 
I/O like/O them/O ./O 
They/O all/O want/O me/O to/O support/O them/O ./O 
They/O do/O n't/O know/O how/O to/O bring/O it/O about/O ./O 
They/O come/O up/O to/O my/O office/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O meeting/O with/O three/O of/O them/O in/O the/O next/O week/O ./O 
And/O they/O do/O n't/O know/O --/O ``/O Are/O you/O running/O ?/O 
Are/O you/O not/O running/O ?/O 
Could/O we/O have/O your/O support/O ?/O 
What/O do/O we/O do/O ?/O 
How/O do/O we/O do/O it/O ?/O ''/O 
I/O like/O them/O ./O 
And/O I/O hear/O their/O speeches/O ./O 
And/O they/O do/O n't/O talk/O jobs/O and/O they/O do/O n't/O talk/O China/LOCATION ./O 
When/O was/O the/O last/O time/O you/O heard/O China/LOCATION is/O killing/O us/O ?/O 
They/O 're/O devaluing/O their/O currency/O to/O a/O level/O that/O you/O would/O n't/O believe/O ./O 
It/O makes/O it/O impossible/O for/O our/O companies/O to/O compete/O ,/O impossible/O ./O 
They/O 're/O killing/O us/O ./O 
But/O you/O do/O n't/O hear/O that/O from/O anybody/O else/O ./O 
You/O do/O n't/O hear/O it/O from/O anybody/O else/O ./O 
And/O I/O watch/O the/O speeches/O ./O 
Thank/O you/O ./O 
I/O watch/O the/O speeches/O of/O these/O people/O ,/O and/O they/O say/O the/O sun/O will/O rise/O ,/O the/O moon/O will/O set/O ,/O all/O sorts/O of/O wonderful/O things/O will/O happen/O ./O 
And/O people/O are/O saying/O ,/O ``/O What/O 's/O going/O on/O ?/O 
I/O just/O want/O a/O job/O ./O 
Just/O get/O me/O a/O job/O ./O 
I/O do/O n't/O need/O the/O rhetoric/O ./O 
I/O want/O a/O job/O ./O ''/O 
And/O that/O 's/O what/O 's/O happening/O ./O 
And/O it/O 's/O going/O to/O get/O worse/O ,/O because/O remember/O ,/O Obamacare/PERSON really/O kicks/O in/O in/O '/O 16/O ,/O 2016/O ./O 
Obama/PERSON is/O going/O to/O be/O out/O playing/O golf/O ./O 
He/O might/O be/O on/O one/O of/O my/O courses/O ./O 
I/O would/O invite/O him/O ,/O I/O actually/O would/O say/O ./O 
I/O have/O the/O best/O courses/O in/O the/O world/O ,/O so/O I/O 'd/O say/O ,/O you/O what/O ,/O if/O he/O wants/O to/O --/O I/O have/O one/O right/O next/O to/O the/O White/ORGANIZATION House/ORGANIZATION ,/O right/O on/O the/O Potomac/LOCATION ./O 
If/O he/O 'd/O like/O to/O play/O ,/O that/O 's/O fine/O ./O 
In/O fact/O ,/O I/O 'd/O love/O him/O to/O leave/O early/O and/O play/O ,/O that/O would/O be/O a/O very/O good/O thing/O ./O 
But/O Obamacare/PERSON kicks/O in/O in/O 2016/O ./O 
Really/O big/O league/O ./O 
It/O is/O going/O to/O be/O amazingly/O destructive/O ./O 
Doctors/O are/O quitting/O ./O 
I/O have/O a/O friend/O who/O 's/O a/O doctor/O ,/O and/O he/O said/O to/O me/O the/O other/O day/O ,/O ``/O Donald/PERSON ,/O I/O never/O saw/O anything/O like/O it/O ./O 
I/O have/O more/O accountants/O than/O I/O have/O nurses/O ./O 
It/O 's/O a/O disaster/O ./O 
My/O patients/O are/O beside/O themselves/O ./O 
They/O had/O a/O plan/O that/O was/O good/O ./O 
They/O have/O no/O plan/O now/O ./O ''/O 
We/O have/O to/O repeal/O Obamacare/PERSON ,/O and/O it/O can/O be/O --/O and/O --/O and/O it/O can/O be/O replaced/O with/O something/O much/O better/O for/O everybody/O ./O 
Let/O it/O be/O for/O everybody/O ./O 
But/O much/O better/O and/O much/O less/O expensive/O for/O people/O and/O for/O the/O government/O ./O 
And/O we/O can/O do/O it/O ./O 
So/O I/O 've/O watched/O the/O politicians/O ./O 
I/O 've/O dealt/O with/O them/O all/O my/O life/O ./O 
If/O you/O ca/O n't/O make/O a/O good/O deal/O with/O a/O politician/O ,/O then/O there/O 's/O something/O wrong/O with/O you/O ./O 
You/O 're/O certainly/O not/O very/O good/O ./O 
And/O that/O 's/O what/O we/O have/O =/O representing/O us/O ./O 
They/O will/O never/O make/O America/LOCATION great/O again/O ./O 
They/O do/O n't/O even/O have/O a/O chance/O ./O 
They/O 're/O controlled/O fully/O --/O they/O 're/O controlled/O fully/O by/O the/O lobbyists/O ,/O by/O the/O donors/O ,/O and/O by/O the/O special/O interests/O ,/O fully/O ./O 
Yes/O ,/O they/O control/O them/O ./O 
Hey/O ,/O I/O have/O lobbyists/O ./O 
I/O have/O to/O tell/O you/O ./O 
I/O have/O lobbyists/O that/O can/O produce/O anything/O for/O me/O ./O 
They/O 're/O great/O ./O 
But/O you/O know/O what/O ?/O 
it/O wo/O n't/O happen/O ./O 
It/O wo/O n't/O happen/O ./O 
Because/O we/O have/O to/O stop/O doing/O things/O for/O some/O people/O ,/O but/O for/O this/O country/O ,/O it/O 's/O destroying/O our/O country/O ./O 
We/O have/O to/O stop/O ,/O and/O it/O has/O to/O stop/O now/O ./O 
Now/O ,/O our/O country/O needs/O --/O our/O country/O needs/O a/O truly/O great/O leader/O ,/O and/O we/O need/O a/O truly/O great/O leader/O now/O ./O 
We/O need/O a/O leader/O that/O wrote/O ``/O The/O Art/O of/O the/O Deal/O ./O ''/O 
We/O need/O a/O leader/O that/O can/O bring/O back/O our/O jobs/O ,/O can/O bring/O back/O our/O manufacturing/O ,/O can/O bring/O back/O our/O military/O ,/O can/O take/O care/O of/O our/O vets/O ./O 
Our/O vets/O have/O been/O abandoned/O ./O 
And/O we/O also/O need/O a/O cheerleader/O ./O 
You/O know/O ,/O when/O President/O Obama/PERSON was/O elected/O ,/O I/O said/O ,/O ``/O Well/O ,/O the/O one/O thing/O ,/O I/O think/O he/O 'll/O do/O well/O ./O 
I/O think/O he/O 'll/O be/O a/O great/O cheerleader/O for/O the/O country/O ./O 
I/O think/O he/O 'd/O be/O a/O great/O spirit/O ./O ''/O 
He/O was/O vibrant/O ./O 
He/O was/O young/O ./O 
I/O really/O thought/O that/O he/O would/O be/O a/O great/O cheerleader/O ./O 
He/O 's/O not/O a/O leader/O ./O 
That/O 's/O true/O ./O 
You/O 're/O right/O about/O that/O ./O 
But/O he/O was/O n't/O a/O cheerleader/O ./O 
He/O 's/O actually/O a/O negative/O force/O ./O 
He/O 's/O been/O a/O negative/O force/O ./O 
He/O was/O n't/O a/O cheerleader/O ;/O he/O was/O the/O opposite/O ./O 
We/O need/O somebody/O that/O can/O take/O the/O brand/O of/O the/O United/LOCATION States/LOCATION and/O make/O it/O great/O again/O ./O 
It/O 's/O not/O great/O again/O ./O 
We/O need/O --/O we/O need/O somebody/O --/O we/O need/O somebody/O that/O literally/O will/O take/O this/O country/O and/O make/O it/O great/O again/O ./O 
We/O can/O do/O that/O ./O 
And/O ,/O I/O will/O tell/O you/O ,/O I/O love/O my/O life/O ./O 
I/O have/O a/O wonderful/O family/O ./O 
They/O 're/O saying/O ,/O ``/O Dad/O ,/O you/O 're/O going/O to/O do/O something/O that/O 's/O going/O to/O be/O so/O tough/O ./O ''/O 
You/O know/O ,/O all/O of/O my/O life/O ,/O I/O 've/O heard/O that/O a/O truly/O successful/O person/O ,/O a/O really/O ,/O really/O successful/O person/O and/O even/O modestly/O successful/O can/O not/O run/O for/O public/O office/O ./O 
Just/O ca/O n't/O happen/O ./O 
And/O yet/O that/O 's/O the/O kind/O of/O mindset/O that/O you/O need/O to/O make/O this/O country/O great/O again/O ./O 
So/O ladies/O and/O gentlemen/O ,/O I/O am/O officially/O running/O for/O president/O of/O the/O United/LOCATION States/LOCATION ,/O and/O we/O are/O going/O to/O make/O our/O country/O great/O again/O ./O 
It/O can/O happen/O ./O 
Our/O country/O has/O tremendous/O potential/O ./O 
We/O have/O tremendous/O people/O ./O 
We/O have/O people/O that/O are/O n't/O working/O ./O 
We/O have/O people/O that/O have/O no/O incentive/O to/O work/O ./O 
But/O they/O 're/O going/O to/O have/O incentive/O to/O work/O ,/O because/O the/O greatest/O social/O program/O is/O a/O job/O ./O 
And/O they/O 'll/O be/O proud/O ,/O and/O they/O 'll/O love/O it/O ,/O and/O they/O 'll/O make/O much/O more/O than/O they/O would/O 've/O ever/O made/O ,/O and/O they/O 'll/O be/O --/O they/O 'll/O be/O doing/O so/O well/O ,/O and/O we/O 're/O going/O to/O be/O thriving/O as/O a/O country/O ,/O thriving/O ./O 
It/O can/O happen/O ./O 
I/O will/O be/O the/O greatest/O jobs/O president/O that/O God/O ever/O created/O ./O 
I/O tell/O you/O that/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O bring/O back/O our/O jobs/O from/O China/LOCATION ,/O from/O Mexico/LOCATION ,/O from/O Japan/LOCATION ,/O from/O so/O many/O places/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O bring/O back/O our/O jobs/O ,/O and/O I/O 'll/O bring/O back/O our/O money/O ./O 
Right/O now/O ,/O think/O of/O this/O :/O We/O owe/O China/LOCATION $/O 1.3/O trillion/O ./O 
We/O owe/O Japan/LOCATION more/O than/O that/O ./O 
So/O they/O come/O in/O ,/O they/O take/O our/O jobs/O ,/O they/O take/O our/O money/O ,/O and/O then/O they/O loan/O us/O back/O the/O money/O ,/O and/O we/O pay/O them/O in/O interest/O ,/O and/O then/O the/O dollar/O goes/O up/O so/O their/O deal/O 's/O even/O better/O ./O 
How/O stupid/O are/O our/O leaders/O ?/O 
How/O stupid/O are/O these/O politicians/O to/O allow/O this/O to/O happen/O ?/O 
How/O stupid/O are/O they/O ?/O 
I/O 'm/O going/O to/O tell/O you/O --/O thank/O you/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O going/O to/O tell/O you/O a/O couple/O of/O stories/O about/O trade/O ,/O because/O I/O 'm/O totally/O against/O the/O trade/O bill/O for/O a/O number/O of/O reasons/O ./O 
Number/O one/O ,/O the/O people/O negotiating/O do/O n't/O have/O a/O clue/O ./O 
Our/O president/O does/O n't/O have/O a/O clue/O ./O 
He/O 's/O a/O bad/O negotiator/O ./O 
He/O 's/O the/O one/O that/O did/O Bergdahl/PERSON ./O 
We/O get/O Bergdahl/PERSON ,/O they/O get/O five/O killer/O terrorists/O that/O everybody/O wanted/O over/O there/O ./O 
We/O get/O Bergdahl/PERSON ./O 
We/O get/O a/O traitor/O ./O 
We/O get/O a/O no-good/O traitor/O ,/O and/O they/O get/O the/O five/O people/O that/O they/O wanted/O for/O years/O ,/O and/O those/O people/O are/O now/O back/O on/O the/O battlefield/O trying/O to/O kill/O us/O ./O 
That/O 's/O the/O negotiator/O we/O have/O ./O 
Take/O a/O look/O at/O the/O deal/O he/O 's/O making/O with/O Iran/LOCATION ./O 
He/O makes/O that/O deal/O ,/O Israel/LOCATION maybe/O wo/O n't/O exist/O very/O long/O ./O 
It/O 's/O a/O disaster/O ,/O and/O we/O have/O to/O protect/O Israel/LOCATION ./O 
But/O .../O So/O we/O need/O people/O --/O I/O 'm/O a/O free/O trader/O ./O 
But/O the/O problem/O with/O free/O trade/O is/O you/O need/O really/O talented/O people/O to/O negotiate/O for/O you/O ./O 
If/O you/O do/O n't/O have/O talented/O people/O ,/O if/O you/O do/O n't/O have/O great/O leadership/O ,/O if/O you/O do/O n't/O have/O people/O that/O know/O business/O ,/O not/O just/O a/O political/O hack/O that/O got/O the/O job/O because/O he/O made/O a/O contribution/O to/O a/O campaign/O ,/O which/O is/O the/O way/O all/O jobs/O ,/O just/O about/O ,/O are/O gotten/O ,/O free/O trade/O terrible/O ./O 
Free/O trade/O can/O be/O wonderful/O if/O you/O have/O smart/O people/O ,/O but/O we/O have/O people/O that/O are/O stupid/O ./O 
We/O have/O people/O that/O are/O n't/O smart/O ./O 
And/O we/O have/O people/O that/O are/O controlled/O by/O special/O interests/O ./O 
And/O it/O 's/O just/O not/O going/O to/O work/O ./O 
So/O ,/O here/O 's/O a/O couple/O of/O stories/O happened/O recently/O ./O 
A/O friend/O of/O mine/O is/O a/O great/O manufacturer/O ./O 
And/O ,/O you/O know/O ,/O China/LOCATION comes/O over/O and/O they/O dump/O all/O their/O stuff/O ,/O and/O I/O buy/O it/O ./O 
I/O buy/O it/O ,/O because/O ,/O frankly/O ,/O I/O have/O an/O obligation/O to/O buy/O it/O ,/O because/O they/O devalue/O their/O currency/O so/O brilliantly/O ,/O they/O just/O did/O it/O recently/O ,/O and/O nobody/O thought/O they/O could/O do/O it/O again/O ./O 
But/O with/O all/O our/O problems/O with/O Russia/LOCATION ,/O with/O all/O our/O problems/O with/O everything/O --/O everything/O ,/O they/O got/O away/O with/O it/O again/O ./O 
And/O it/O 's/O impossible/O for/O our/O people/O here/O to/O compete/O ./O 
So/O I/O want/O to/O tell/O you/O this/O story/O ./O 
A/O friend/O of/O mine/O who/O 's/O a/O great/O manufacturer/O ,/O calls/O me/O up/O a/O few/O weeks/O ago/O ./O 
He/O 's/O very/O upset/O ./O 
I/O said/O ,/O ``/O What/O 's/O your/O problem/O ?/O ''/O 
He/O said/O ,/O ``/O You/O know/O ,/O I/O make/O great/O product/O ./O ''/O 
And/O I/O said/O ,/O ``/O I/O know/O ./O 
I/O know/O that/O because/O I/O buy/O the/O product/O ./O ''/O 
He/O said/O ,/O ``/O I/O ca/O n't/O get/O it/O into/O China/LOCATION ./O 
They/O wo/O n't/O accept/O it/O ./O 
I/O sent/O a/O boat/O over/O and/O they/O actually/O sent/O it/O back/O ./O 
They/O talked/O about/O environmental/O ,/O they/O talked/O about/O all/O sorts/O of/O crap/O that/O had/O nothing/O to/O do/O with/O it/O ./O ''/O 
I/O said/O ,/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O wait/O a/O minute/O ,/O that/O 's/O terrible/O ./O 
Does/O anyone/O know/O this/O ?/O ''/O 
He/O said/O ,/O ``/O Yeah/O ,/O they/O do/O it/O all/O the/O time/O with/O other/O people/O ./O ''/O 
I/O said/O ,/O ``/O They/O send/O it/O back/O ?/O ''/O 
``/O Yeah/O ./O 
So/O I/O finally/O got/O it/O over/O there/O and/O they/O charged/O me/O a/O big/O tariff/O ./O 
They/O 're/O not/O supposed/O to/O be/O doing/O that/O ./O 
I/O told/O them/O ./O ''/O 
Now/O ,/O they/O do/O charge/O you/O tariff/O on/O trucks/O ,/O when/O we/O send/O trucks/O and/O other/O things/O over/O there/O ./O 
Ask/O Boeing/ORGANIZATION ./O 
They/O wanted/O Boeing/ORGANIZATION 's/O secrets/O ./O 
They/O wanted/O their/O patents/O and/O all/O their/O secrets/O before/O they/O agreed/O to/O buy/O planes/O from/O Boeing/ORGANIZATION ./O 
Hey/O ,/O I/O 'm/O not/O saying/O they/O 're/O stupid/O ./O 
I/O like/O China/LOCATION ./O 
I/O sell/O apartments/O for/O --/O I/O just/O sold/O an/O apartment/O for/O $/O 15/O million/O to/O somebody/O from/O China/LOCATION ./O 
Am/O I/O supposed/O to/O dislike/O them/O ?/O 
I/O own/O a/O big/O chunk/O of/O the/O Bank/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION America/ORGANIZATION Building/ORGANIZATION at/O 1290/O Avenue/O of/O the/O Americas/LOCATION ,/O that/O I/O got/O from/O China/LOCATION in/O a/O war/O ./O 
Very/O valuable/O ./O 
I/O love/O China/LOCATION ./O 
The/O biggest/O bank/O in/O the/O world/O is/O from/O China/LOCATION ./O 
You/O know/O where/O their/O United/LOCATION States/LOCATION headquarters/O is/O located/O ?/O 
In/O this/O building/O ,/O in/O Trump/LOCATION Tower/LOCATION ./O 
I/O love/O China/LOCATION ./O 
People/O say/O ,/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O you/O do/O n't/O like/O China/LOCATION ?/O ''/O 
No/O ,/O I/O love/O them/O ./O 
But/O their/O leaders/O are/O much/O smarter/O than/O our/O leaders/O ,/O and/O we/O ca/O n't/O sustain/O ourself/O with/O that/O ./O 
There/O 's/O too/O much/O --/O it/O 's/O like/O --/O it/O 's/O like/O take/O the/O New/ORGANIZATION England/ORGANIZATION Patriots/ORGANIZATION and/O Tom/PERSON Brady/PERSON and/O have/O them/O play/O your/O high/O school/O football/O team/O ./O 
That/O 's/O the/O difference/O between/O China/LOCATION 's/O leaders/O and/O our/O leaders/O ./O 
They/O are/O ripping/O us/O ./O 
We/O are/O rebuilding/O China/LOCATION ./O 
We/O 're/O rebuilding/O many/O countries/O ./O 
China/LOCATION ,/O you/O go/O there/O now/O ,/O roads/O ,/O bridges/O ,/O schools/O ,/O you/O never/O saw/O anything/O like/O it/O ./O 
They/O have/O bridges/O that/O make/O the/O George/LOCATION Washington/LOCATION Bridge/LOCATION look/O like/O small/O potatoes/O ./O 
And/O they/O 're/O all/O over/O the/O place/O ./O 
We/O have/O all/O the/O cards/O ,/O but/O we/O do/O n't/O know/O how/O to/O use/O them/O ./O 
We/O do/O n't/O even/O know/O that/O we/O have/O the/O cards/O ,/O because/O our/O leaders/O do/O n't/O understand/O the/O game/O ./O 
We/O could/O turn/O off/O that/O spigot/O by/O charging/O them/O tax/O until/O they/O behave/O properly/O ./O 
Now/O they/O 're/O going/O militarily/O ./O 
They/O 're/O building/O a/O military/O island/O in/O the/O middle/O of/O the/O South/LOCATION China/LOCATION sea/O ./O 
A/O military/O island/O ./O 
Now/O ,/O our/O country/O could/O never/O do/O that/O because/O we/O 'd/O have/O to/O get/O environmental/O clearance/O ,/O and/O the/O environmentalist/O would/O n't/O let/O our/O country/O --/O we/O would/O never/O build/O in/O an/O ocean/O ./O 
They/O built/O it/O in/O about/O one/O year/O ,/O this/O massive/O military/O port/O ./O 
They/O 're/O building/O up/O their/O military/O to/O a/O point/O that/O is/O very/O scary/O ./O 
You/O have/O a/O problem/O with/O ISIS/ORGANIZATION ./O 
You/O have/O a/O bigger/O problem/O with/O China/LOCATION ./O 
And/O ,/O in/O my/O opinion/O ,/O the/O new/O China/LOCATION ,/O believe/O it/O or/O not/O ,/O in/O terms/O of/O trade/O ,/O is/O Mexico/LOCATION ./O 
So/O this/O man/O tells/O me/O about/O the/O manufacturing/O ./O 
I/O say/O ,/O ``/O That/O 's/O a/O terrible/O story/O ./O 
I/O hate/O to/O hear/O it/O ./O ''/O 
But/O I/O have/O another/O one/O ,/O Ford/ORGANIZATION ./O 
So/O Mexico/LOCATION takes/O a/O company/O ,/O a/O car/O company/O that/O was/O going/O to/O build/O in/O Tennessee/LOCATION ,/O rips/O it/O out/O ./O 
Everybody/O thought/O the/O deal/O was/O dead/O ./O 
Reported/O it/O in/O the/O Wall/ORGANIZATION Street/ORGANIZATION Journal/ORGANIZATION recently/O ./O 
Everybody/O thought/O it/O was/O a/O done/O deal/O ./O 
It/O 's/O going/O in/O and/O that/O 's/O going/O to/O be/O it/O ,/O going/O into/O Tennessee/LOCATION ./O 
Great/O state/O ,/O great/O people/O ./O 
All/O of/O a/O sudden/O ,/O at/O the/O last/O moment/O ,/O this/O big/O car/O manufacturer/O ,/O foreign/O ,/O announces/O they/O 're/O not/O going/O to/O Tennessee/LOCATION ./O 
They/O 're/O gon/O na/O spend/O their/O $/O 1/O billion/O in/O Mexico/LOCATION instead/O ./O 
Not/O good/O ./O 
Now/O ,/O Ford/ORGANIZATION announces/O a/O few/O weeks/O ago/O that/O Ford/ORGANIZATION is/O going/O to/O build/O a/O $/O 2.5/O billion/O car/O and/O truck/O and/O parts/O manufacturing/O plant/O in/O Mexico/LOCATION ./O 
$/O 2.5/O billion/O ,/O it/O 's/O going/O to/O be/O one/O of/O the/O largest/O in/O the/O world/O ./O 
Ford/ORGANIZATION ./O 
Good/O company/O ./O 
So/O I/O announced/O that/O I/O 'm/O running/O for/O president/O ./O 
I/O would/O one/O of/O the/O early/O things/O I/O would/O do/O ,/O probably/O before/O I/O even/O got/O in/O --/O and/O I/O would/O n't/O even/O use/O --/O you/O know/O ,/O I/O have/O --/O I/O know/O the/O smartest/O negotiators/O in/O the/O world/O ./O 
I/O know/O the/O good/O ones/O ./O 
I/O know/O the/O bad/O ones/O ./O 
I/O know/O the/O overrated/O ones/O ./O 
You/O get/O a/O lot/O of/O them/O that/O are/O overrated/O ./O 
They/O 're/O not/O good/O ./O 
They/O think/O they/O are/O ./O 
They/O get/O good/O stories/O ,/O because/O the/O newspapers/O get/O buffaloed/O -LRB-/O ph/O -RRB-/O ./O 
But/O they/O 're/O not/O good/O ./O 
But/O I/O know/O the/O negotiators/O in/O the/O world/O ,/O and/O I/O put/O them/O one/O for/O each/O country/O ./O 
Believe/O me/O ,/O folks/O ./O 
We/O will/O do/O very/O ,/O very/O well/O ,/O very/O ,/O very/O well/O ./O 
But/O I/O would/O n't/O even/O waste/O my/O time/O with/O this/O one/O ./O 
I/O would/O call/O up/O the/O head/O of/O Ford/ORGANIZATION ,/O who/O I/O know/O ./O 
If/O I/O was/O president/O ,/O I/O 'd/O say/O ,/O ``/O Congratulations/O ./O 
I/O understand/O that/O you/O 're/O building/O a/O nice/O $/O 2.5/O billion/O car/O factory/O in/O Mexico/LOCATION and/O that/O you/O 're/O going/O to/O take/O your/O cars/O and/O sell/O them/O to/O the/O United/LOCATION States/LOCATION zero/O tax/O ,/O just/O flow/O them/O across/O the/O border/O ./O ''/O 
And/O you/O say/O to/O yourself/O ,/O ``/O How/O does/O that/O help/O us/O ,/O ''/O right/O ?/O 
``/O How/O does/O that/O help/O us/O ?/O 
Where/O is/O that/O good/O ''/O ?/O 
It/O 's/O not/O ./O 
So/O I/O would/O say/O ,/O ``/O Congratulations/O ./O 
That/O 's/O the/O good/O news/O ./O 
Let/O me/O give/O you/O the/O bad/O news/O ./O 
Every/O car/O and/O every/O truck/O and/O every/O part/O manufactured/O in/O this/O plant/O that/O comes/O across/O the/O border/O ,/O we/O 're/O going/O to/O charge/O you/O a/O 35-percent/O tax/O ,/O and/O that/O tax/O is/O going/O to/O be/O paid/O simultaneously/O with/O the/O transaction/O ,/O and/O that/O 's/O it/O ./O 
Now/O ,/O here/O 's/O what/O is/O going/O to/O happen/O ./O 
If/O it/O 's/O not/O me/O in/O the/O position/O ,/O it/O 's/O one/O of/O these/O politicians/O that/O we/O 're/O running/O against/O ,/O you/O know/O ,/O the/O 400/O people/O that/O we/O 're/O -LRB-/O inaudible/O -RRB-/O ./O 
And/O here/O 's/O what/O 's/O going/O to/O happen/O ./O 
They/O 're/O not/O so/O stupid/O ./O 
They/O know/O it/O 's/O not/O a/O good/O thing/O ,/O and/O they/O may/O even/O be/O upset/O by/O it/O ./O 
But/O then/O they/O 're/O going/O to/O get/O a/O call/O from/O the/O donors/O or/O probably/O from/O the/O lobbyist/O for/O Ford/ORGANIZATION and/O say/O ,/O ``/O You/O ca/O n't/O do/O that/O to/O Ford/ORGANIZATION ,/O because/O Ford/ORGANIZATION takes/O care/O of/O me/O and/O I/O take/O care/O of/O you/O ,/O and/O you/O ca/O n't/O do/O that/O to/O Ford/ORGANIZATION ./O ''/O 
And/O guess/O what/O ?/O 
No/O problem/O ./O 
They/O 're/O going/O to/O build/O in/O Mexico/LOCATION ./O 
They/O 're/O going/O to/O take/O away/O thousands/O of/O jobs/O ./O 
It/O 's/O very/O bad/O for/O us/O ./O 
So/O under/O President/O Trump/PERSON ,/O here/O 's/O what/O would/O happen/O :/O The/O head/O of/O Ford/ORGANIZATION will/O call/O me/O back/O ,/O I/O would/O say/O within/O an/O hour/O after/O I/O told/O them/O the/O bad/O news/O ./O 
But/O it/O could/O be/O he/O 'd/O want/O to/O be/O cool/O ,/O and/O he/O 'll/O wait/O until/O the/O next/O day/O ./O 
You/O know/O ,/O they/O want/O to/O be/O a/O little/O cool/O ./O 
And/O he/O 'll/O say/O ,/O ``/O Please/O ,/O please/O ,/O please/O ./O ''/O 
He/O 'll/O beg/O for/O a/O little/O while/O ,/O and/O I/O 'll/O say/O ,/O ``/O No/O interest/O ./O ''/O 
Then/O he/O 'll/O call/O all/O sorts/O of/O political/O people/O ,/O and/O I/O 'll/O say/O ,/O ``/O Sorry/O ,/O fellas/O ./O 
No/O interest/O ,/O ''/O because/O I/O do/O n't/O need/O anybody/O 's/O money/O ./O 
It/O 's/O nice/O ./O 
I/O do/O n't/O need/O anybody/O 's/O money/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O using/O my/O own/O money/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O not/O using/O the/O lobbyists/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O not/O using/O donors/O ./O 
I/O do/O n't/O care/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O really/O rich/O ./O 
I/O -LRB-/O inaudible/O -RRB-/O ./O 
And/O by/O the/O way/O ,/O I/O 'm/O not/O even/O saying/O that/O in/O a/O --/O that/O 's/O the/O kind/O of/O mindset/O ,/O that/O 's/O the/O kind/O of/O thinking/O you/O need/O for/O this/O country/O ./O 
So/O --/O because/O we/O got/O to/O make/O the/O country/O rich/O ./O 
It/O sounds/O crass/O ./O 
Somebody/O said/O ,/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O that/O 's/O crass/O ./O ''/O 
It/O 's/O not/O crass/O ./O 
We/O got/O $/O 18/O trillion/O in/O debt/O ./O 
We/O got/O nothing/O but/O problems/O ./O 
We/O got/O a/O military/O that/O needs/O equipment/O all/O over/O the/O place/O ./O 
We/O got/O nuclear/O weapons/O that/O are/O obsolete/O ./O 
We/O 've/O got/O nothing/O ./O 
We/O 've/O got/O Social/ORGANIZATION Security/ORGANIZATION that/O 's/O going/O to/O be/O destroyed/O if/O somebody/O like/O me/O does/O n't/O bring/O money/O into/O the/O country/O ./O 
All/O these/O other/O people/O want/O to/O cut/O the/O hell/O out/O of/O it/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O not/O going/O to/O cut/O it/O at/O all/O ;/O I/O 'm/O going/O to/O bring/O money/O in/O ,/O and/O we/O 're/O going/O to/O save/O it/O ./O 
But/O here/O 's/O what/O 's/O going/O to/O happen/O :/O After/O I/O 'm/O called/O by/O 30/O friends/O of/O mine/O who/O contributed/O to/O different/O campaigns/O ,/O after/O I/O 'm/O called/O by/O all/O of/O the/O special/O interests/O and/O by/O the/O --/O the/O donors/O and/O by/O the/O lobbyists/O --/O and/O they/O have/O zero/O chance/O at/O convincing/O me/O ,/O zero/O --/O I/O 'll/O get/O a/O call/O the/O next/O day/O from/O the/O head/O of/O Ford/ORGANIZATION ./O 
He/O 'll/O say/O ./O 
``/O Please/O reconsider/O ,/O ''/O I/O 'll/O say/O no/O ./O 
He/O 'll/O say/O ,/O ``/O Mr./O President/O ,/O we/O 've/O decided/O to/O move/O the/O plant/O back/O to/O the/O United/LOCATION States/LOCATION ,/O and/O we/O 're/O not/O going/O to/O build/O it/O in/O Mexico/LOCATION ./O ''/O 
That/O 's/O it/O ./O 
They/O have/O no/O choice/O ./O 
They/O have/O no/O choice/O ./O 
There/O are/O hundreds/O of/O things/O like/O that/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O give/O you/O another/O example/O ./O 
Saudi/LOCATION Arabia/LOCATION ,/O they/O make/O $/O 1/O billion/O a/O day/O ./O 
$/O 1/O billion/O a/O day/O ./O 
I/O love/O the/O Saudis/O ./O 
Many/O are/O in/O this/O building/O ./O 
They/O make/O a/O billion/O dollars/O a/O day/O ./O 
Whenever/O they/O have/O problems/O ,/O we/O send/O over/O the/O ships/O ./O 
We/O say/O ``/O we/O 're/O gon/O na/O protect/O ./O ''/O 
What/O are/O we/O doing/O ?/O 
They/O 've/O got/O nothing/O but/O money/O ./O 
If/O the/O right/O person/O asked/O them/O ,/O they/O 'd/O pay/O a/O fortune/O ./O 
They/O would/O n't/O be/O there/O except/O for/O us/O ./O 
And/O believe/O me/O ,/O you/O look/O at/O the/O border/O with/O Yemen/LOCATION ./O 
You/O remember/O Obama/PERSON a/O year/O ago/O ,/O Yemen/LOCATION was/O a/O great/O victory/O ./O 
Two/O weeks/O later/O ,/O the/O place/O was/O blown/O up/O ./O 
Everybody/O got/O out/O --/O and/O they/O kept/O our/O equipment/O ./O 
They/O always/O keep/O our/O equipment/O ./O 
We/O ought/O to/O send/O used/O equipment/O ,/O right/O ?/O 
They/O always/O keep/O our/O equipment/O ./O 
We/O ought/O to/O send/O some/O real/O junk/O ,/O because/O ,/O frankly/O ,/O it/O would/O be/O --/O we/O ought/O to/O send/O our/O surplus/O ./O 
We/O 're/O always/O losing/O this/O gorgeous/O brand-new/O stuff/O ./O 
But/O look/O at/O that/O border/O with/O Saudi/LOCATION Arabia/LOCATION ./O 
Do/O you/O really/O think/O that/O these/O people/O are/O interested/O in/O Yemen/LOCATION ?/O 
Saudi/LOCATION Arabia/LOCATION without/O us/O is/O gone/O ./O 
They/O ;/O re/O gone/O ./O 
And/O I/O 'm/O the/O one/O that/O made/O all/O of/O the/O right/O predictions/O about/O Iraq/LOCATION ./O 
You/O know/O ,/O all/O of/O these/O politicians/O that/O I/O 'm/O running/O against/O now/O --/O it/O 's/O so/O nice/O to/O say/O I/O 'm/O running/O as/O opposed/O to/O if/O I/O run/O ,/O if/O I/O run/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O running/O ./O 
But/O all/O of/O these/O politicians/O that/O I/O 'm/O running/O against/O now/O ,/O they/O 're/O trying/O to/O disassociate/O ./O 
I/O mean/O ,/O you/O looked/O at/O Bush/PERSON ,/O it/O took/O him/O five/O days/O to/O answer/O the/O question/O on/O Iraq/LOCATION ./O 
He/O could/O n't/O answer/O the/O question/O ./O 
He/O did/O n't/O know/O ./O 
I/O said/O ,/O ``/O Is/O he/O intelligent/O ?/O ''/O 
Then/O I/O looked/O at/O Rubio/PERSON ./O 
He/O was/O unable/O to/O answer/O the/O question/O ,/O is/O Iraq/LOCATION a/O good/O thing/O or/O bad/O thing/O ?/O 
He/O did/O n't/O know/O ./O 
He/O could/O n't/O answer/O the/O question/O ./O 
How/O are/O these/O people/O gon/O na/O lead/O us/O ?/O 
How/O are/O we/O gon/O na/O --/O how/O are/O we/O gon/O na/O go/O back/O and/O make/O it/O great/O again/O ?/O 
We/O ca/O n't/O ./O 
They/O do/O n't/O have/O a/O clue/O ./O 
They/O ca/O n't/O lead/O us/O ./O 
They/O ca/O n't/O ./O 
They/O ca/O n't/O even/O answer/O simple/O questions/O ./O 
It/O was/O terrible/O ./O 
But/O Saudi/LOCATION Arabia/LOCATION is/O in/O big/O ,/O big/O trouble/O ./O 
Now/O ,/O thanks/O to/O fracking/O and/O other/O things/O ,/O the/O oil/O is/O all/O over/O the/O place/O ./O 
And/O I/O used/O to/O say/O it/O ,/O there/O are/O ships/O at/O sea/O ,/O and/O this/O was/O during/O the/O worst/O crisis/O ,/O that/O were/O loaded/O up/O with/O oil/O ,/O and/O the/O cartel/O kept/O the/O price/O up/O ,/O because/O ,/O again/O ,/O they/O were/O smarter/O than/O our/O leaders/O ./O 
They/O were/O smarter/O than/O our/O leaders/O ./O 
There/O is/O so/O much/O wealth/O out/O there/O that/O can/O make/O our/O country/O so/O rich/O again/O ,/O and/O therefore/O make/O it/O great/O again/O ./O 
Because/O we/O need/O money/O ./O 
We/O 're/O dying/O ./O 
We/O 're/O dying/O ./O 
We/O need/O money/O ./O 
We/O have/O to/O do/O it/O ./O 
And/O we/O need/O the/O right/O people/O ./O 
So/O Ford/ORGANIZATION will/O come/O back/O ./O 
They/O 'll/O all/O come/O back/O ./O 
And/O I/O will/O say/O this/O ,/O this/O is/O going/O to/O be/O an/O election/O ,/O in/O my/O opinion/O ,/O that/O 's/O based/O on/O competence/O ./O 
Somebody/O said/O --/O thank/O you/O ,/O darlin/O '/O ./O 
Somebody/O said/O to/O me/O the/O other/O day/O ,/O a/O reporter/O ,/O a/O very/O nice/O reporter/O ,/O ``/O But/O ,/O Mr./O Trump/PERSON ,/O you/O 're/O not/O a/O nice/O person/O ./O ''/O 
That/O 's/O true/O ./O 
But/O actually/O I/O am/O ./O 
I/O think/O I/O am/O a/O nice/O person/O ./O 
People/O that/O know/O me/O ,/O like/O me/O ./O 
Does/O my/O family/O like/O me/O ?/O 
I/O think/O so/O ,/O right/O ./O 
Look/O at/O my/O family/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O proud/O of/O my/O family/O ./O 
Great/O ./O 
Jared/PERSON -LRB-/O ph/O -RRB-/O ,/O Laura/PERSON and/O Eric/PERSON ,/O I/O 'm/O very/O proud/O of/O my/O family/O ./O 
They/O 're/O a/O great/O family/O ./O 
So/O the/O reporter/O said/O to/O me/O the/O other/O day/O ,/O ``/O But/O ,/O Mr./O Trump/PERSON ,/O you/O 're/O not/O a/O nice/O person/O ./O 
How/O can/O you/O get/O people/O to/O vote/O for/O you/O ?/O ''/O 
I/O said/O ,/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O know/O ./O ''/O 
I/O said/O ,/O ``/O I/O think/O that/O number/O one/O ,/O I/O am/O a/O nice/O person/O ./O 
I/O give/O a/O lot/O of/O money/O away/O to/O charities/O and/O other/O things/O ./O 
I/O think/O I/O 'm/O actually/O a/O very/O nice/O person/O ./O ''/O 
But/O ,/O I/O said/O ,/O ``/O This/O is/O going/O to/O be/O an/O election/O that/O 's/O based/O on/O competence/O ,/O because/O people/O are/O tired/O of/O these/O nice/O people/O ./O 
And/O they/O 're/O tired/O of/O being/O ripped/O off/O by/O everybody/O in/O the/O world/O ./O 
And/O they/O 're/O tired/O of/O spending/O more/O money/O on/O education/O than/O any/O nation/O in/O the/O world/O per/O capita/O ,/O than/O any/O nation/O in/O the/O world/O ,/O and/O we/O are/O 26th/O in/O the/O world/O ,/O 25/O countries/O are/O better/O than/O us/O in/O education/O ./O 
And/O some/O of/O them/O are/O like/O third/O world/O countries/O ./O 
But/O we/O 're/O becoming/O a/O third/O word/O country/O ,/O because/O of/O our/O infrastructure/O ,/O our/O airports/O ,/O our/O roads/O ,/O everything/O ./O 
So/O one/O of/O the/O things/O I/O did/O ,/O and/O I/O said/O ,/O you/O know/O what/O I/O 'll/O do/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O do/O it/O ./O 
Because/O a/O lot/O of/O people/O said/O ,/O ``/O He/O 'll/O never/O run/O ./O 
Number/O one/O ,/O he/O wo/O n't/O want/O to/O give/O up/O his/O lifestyle/O ./O ''/O 
They/O 're/O right/O about/O that/O ,/O but/O I/O 'm/O doing/O it/O ./O 
Number/O two/O ,/O I/O 'm/O a/O private/O company/O ,/O so/O nobody/O knows/O what/O I/O 'm/O worth/O ./O 
And/O the/O one/O thing/O is/O that/O when/O you/O run/O ,/O you/O have/O to/O announce/O and/O certify/O to/O all/O sorts/O of/O governmental/O authorities/O your/O net/O worth/O ./O 
So/O I/O said/O ,/O ``/O That/O 's/O OK/O ./O ''/O 
I/O 'm/O proud/O of/O my/O net/O worth/O ./O 
I/O 've/O done/O an/O amazing/O job/O ./O 
I/O started/O off/O --/O thank/O you/O --/O I/O started/O off/O in/O a/O small/O office/O with/O my/O father/O in/O Brooklyn/LOCATION and/O Queens/LOCATION ,/O and/O my/O father/O said/O --/O and/O I/O love/O my/O father/O ./O 
I/O learned/O so/O much/O ./O 
He/O was/O a/O great/O negotiator/O ./O 
I/O learned/O so/O much/O just/O sitting/O at/O his/O feet/O playing/O with/O blocks/O listening/O to/O him/O negotiate/O with/O subcontractors/O ./O 
But/O I/O learned/O a/O lot/O ./O 
But/O he/O used/O to/O say/O ,/O ``/O Donald/PERSON ,/O do/O n't/O go/O into/O Manhattan/LOCATION ./O 
That/O 's/O the/O big/O leagues/O ./O 
We/O do/O n't/O know/O anything/O about/O that/O ./O 
Do/O n't/O do/O it/O ./O ''/O 
I/O said/O ,/O ``/O I/O got/O ta/O go/O into/O Manhattan/LOCATION ./O 
I/O got/O ta/O build/O those/O big/O buildings/O ./O 
I/O got/O ta/O do/O it/O ,/O Dad/O ./O 
I/O 've/O got/O ta/O do/O it/O ./O ''/O 
And/O after/O four/O or/O five/O years/O in/O Brooklyn/LOCATION ,/O I/O ventured/O into/O Manhattan/LOCATION and/O did/O a/O lot/O of/O great/O deals/O --/O the/O Grand/LOCATION Hyatt/LOCATION Hotel/LOCATION ./O 
I/O was/O responsible/O for/O the/O convention/O center/O on/O the/O west/O side/O ./O 
I/O did/O a/O lot/O of/O great/O deals/O ,/O and/O I/O did/O them/O early/O and/O young/O ./O 
And/O now/O I/O 'm/O building/O all/O over/O the/O world/O ,/O and/O I/O love/O what/O I/O 'm/O doing/O ./O 
But/O they/O all/O said/O ,/O a/O lot/O of/O the/O pundits/O on/O television/O ,/O ``/O Well/O ,/O Donald/PERSON will/O never/O run/O ,/O and/O one/O of/O the/O main/O reasons/O is/O he/O 's/O private/O and/O he/O 's/O probably/O not/O as/O successful/O as/O everybody/O thinks/O ./O ''/O 
So/O I/O said/O to/O myself/O ,/O you/O know/O ,/O nobody/O 's/O ever/O going/O to/O know/O unless/O I/O run/O ,/O because/O I/O 'm/O really/O proud/O of/O my/O success/O ./O 
I/O really/O am/O ./O 
I/O 've/O employed/O --/O I/O 've/O employed/O tens/O of/O thousands/O of/O people/O over/O my/O lifetime/O ./O 
That/O means/O medical/O ./O 
That/O means/O education/O ./O 
That/O means/O everything/O ./O 
So/O a/O large/O accounting/O firm/O and/O my/O accountants/O have/O been/O working/O for/O months/O ,/O because/O it/O 's/O big/O and/O complex/O ,/O and/O they/O 've/O put/O together/O a/O statement/O ,/O a/O financial/O statement/O ,/O just/O a/O summary/O ./O 
But/O everything/O will/O be/O filed/O eventually/O with/O the/O government/O ,/O and/O we/O do/O n't/O extensions/O or/O anything/O ./O 
We/O 'll/O be/O filing/O it/O right/O on/O time/O ./O 
We/O do/O n't/O need/O anything/O ./O 
And/O it/O was/O even/O reported/O incorrectly/O yesterday/O ,/O because/O they/O said/O ,/O ``/O He/O had/O assets/O of/O $/O 9/O billion/O ./O ''/O 
So/O I/O said/O -LRB-/O ph/O -RRB-/O ,/O ``/O No/O ,/O that/O 's/O the/O wrong/O number/O ./O 
That/O 's/O the/O wrong/O number/O ./O 
Not/O assets/O ./O ''/O 
So/O they/O put/O together/O this/O ./O 
And/O before/O I/O say/O it/O ,/O I/O have/O to/O say/O this/O ./O 
I/O made/O it/O the/O old-fashioned/O way/O ./O 
It/O 's/O real/O estate/O ./O 
You/O know/O ,/O it/O 's/O real/O estate/O ./O 
It/O 's/O labor/O ,/O and/O it/O 's/O unions/O good/O and/O some/O bad/O and/O lots/O of/O people/O that/O are/O n't/O in/O unions/O ,/O and/O it/O 's/O all/O over/O the/O place/O and/O building/O all/O over/O the/O world/O ./O 
And/O I/O have/O assets/O --/O big/O accounting/O firm/O ,/O one/O of/O the/O most/O highly/O respected/O --/O 9/O billion/O 240/O million/O dollars/O ./O 
And/O I/O have/O liabilities/O of/O about/O $/O 500/O million/O -LRB-/O ph/O -RRB-/O ./O 
That/O 's/O long-term/O debt/O ,/O very/O low/O interest/O rates/O ./O 
In/O fact/O ,/O one/O of/O the/O big/O banks/O came/O to/O me/O and/O said/O ,/O ``/O Donald/PERSON ,/O you/O do/O n't/O have/O enough/O borrowings/O ./O 
Could/O we/O loan/O you/O $/O 4/O billion/O ''/O ?/O 
I/O said/O ,/O ``/O I/O do/O n't/O need/O it/O ./O 
I/O do/O n't/O want/O it/O ./O 
And/O I/O 've/O been/O there/O ./O 
I/O do/O n't/O want/O it/O ./O ''/O 
But/O in/O two/O seconds/O ,/O they/O give/O me/O whatever/O I/O wanted/O ./O 
So/O I/O have/O a/O total/O net/O worth/O ,/O and/O now/O with/O the/O increase/O ,/O it/O 'll/O be/O well-over/O $/O 10/O billion/O ./O 
But/O here/O ,/O a/O total/O net/O worth/O of/O --/O net/O worth/O ,/O not/O assets/O ,/O not/O --/O a/O net/O worth/O ,/O after/O all/O debt/O ,/O after/O all/O expenses/O ,/O the/O greatest/O assets/O --/O Trump/LOCATION Tower/LOCATION ,/O 1290/O Avenue/O of/O the/O Americas/LOCATION ,/O Bank/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION America/ORGANIZATION building/O in/O San/LOCATION Francisco/LOCATION ,/O 40/O Wall/O Street/O ,/O sometimes/O referred/O to/O as/O the/O Trump/PERSON building/O right/O opposite/O the/O New/LOCATION York/LOCATION --/O many/O other/O places/O all/O over/O the/O world/O ./O 
So/O the/O total/O is/O $/O 8,737,540,00/O ./O 
Now/O I/O 'm/O not/O doing/O that/O .../O I/O 'm/O not/O doing/O that/O to/O brag/O ,/O because/O you/O know/O what/O ?/O 
I/O do/O n't/O have/O to/O brag/O ./O 
I/O do/O n't/O have/O to/O ,/O believe/O it/O or/O not/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O doing/O that/O to/O say/O that/O that/O 's/O the/O kind/O of/O thinking/O our/O country/O needs/O ./O 
We/O need/O that/O thinking/O ./O 
We/O have/O the/O opposite/O thinking/O ./O 
We/O have/O losers/O ./O 
We/O have/O losers/O ./O 
We/O have/O people/O that/O do/O n't/O have/O it/O ./O 
We/O have/O people/O that/O are/O morally/O corrupt/O ./O 
We/O have/O people/O that/O are/O selling/O this/O country/O down/O the/O drain/O ./O 
So/O I/O put/O together/O this/O statement/O ,/O and/O the/O only/O reason/O I/O 'm/O telling/O you/O about/O it/O today/O is/O because/O we/O really/O do/O have/O to/O get/O going/O ,/O because/O if/O we/O have/O another/O three/O or/O four/O years/O --/O you/O know/O ,/O we/O 're/O at/O $/O 8/O trillion/O now/O ./O 
We/O 're/O soon/O going/O to/O be/O at/O $/O 20/O trillion/O ./O 
According/O to/O the/O economists/O --/O who/O I/O 'm/O not/O big/O believers/O in/O ,/O but/O ,/O nevertheless/O ,/O this/O is/O what/O they/O 're/O saying/O --/O that/O $/O 24/O trillion/O --/O we/O 're/O very/O close/O --/O that/O 's/O the/O point/O of/O no/O return/O ./O 
$/O 24/O trillion/O ./O 
We/O will/O be/O there/O soon/O ./O 
That/O 's/O when/O we/O become/O Greece/LOCATION ./O 
That/O 's/O when/O we/O become/O a/O country/O that/O 's/O unsalvageable/O ./O 
And/O we/O 're/O gon/O na/O be/O there/O very/O soon/O ./O 
We/O 're/O gon/O na/O be/O there/O very/O soon/O ./O 
So/O ,/O just/O to/O sum/O up/O ,/O I/O would/O do/O various/O things/O very/O quickly/O ./O 
I/O would/O repeal/O and/O replace/O the/O big/O lie/O ,/O Obamacare/PERSON ./O 
I/O would/O build/O a/O great/O wall/O ,/O and/O nobody/O builds/O walls/O better/O than/O me/O ,/O believe/O me/O ,/O and/O I/O 'll/O build/O them/O very/O inexpensively/O ,/O I/O will/O build/O a/O great/O ,/O great/O wall/O on/O our/O southern/O border/O ./O 
And/O I/O will/O have/O Mexico/LOCATION pay/O for/O that/O wall/O ./O 
Mark/O my/O words/O ./O 
Nobody/O would/O be/O tougher/O on/O ISIS/ORGANIZATION than/O Donald/PERSON Trump/PERSON ./O 
Nobody/O ./O 
I/O will/O find/O --/O within/O our/O military/O ,/O I/O will/O find/O the/O General/O Patton/PERSON or/O I/O will/O find/O General/O MacArthur/PERSON ,/O I/O will/O find/O the/O right/O guy/O ./O 
I/O will/O find/O the/O guy/O that/O 's/O going/O to/O take/O that/O military/O and/O make/O it/O really/O work/O ./O 
Nobody/O ,/O nobody/O will/O be/O pushing/O us/O around/O ./O 
I/O will/O stop/O Iran/LOCATION from/O getting/O nuclear/O weapons/O ./O 
And/O we/O wo/O n't/O be/O using/O a/O man/O like/O Secretary/O Kerry/PERSON that/O has/O absolutely/O no/O concept/O of/O negotiation/O ,/O who/O 's/O making/O a/O horrible/O and/O laughable/O deal/O ,/O who/O 's/O just/O being/O tapped/O along/O as/O they/O make/O weapons/O right/O now/O ,/O and/O then/O goes/O into/O a/O bicycle/O race/O at/O 72/O years/O old/O ,/O and/O falls/O and/O breaks/O his/O leg/O ./O 
I/O wo/O n't/O be/O doing/O that/O ./O 
And/O I/O promise/O I/O will/O never/O be/O in/O a/O bicycle/O race/O ./O 
That/O I/O can/O tell/O you/O ./O 
I/O will/O immediately/O terminate/O President/O Obama/PERSON 's/O illegal/O executive/O order/O on/O immigration/O ,/O immediately/O ./O 
Fully/O support/O and/O back/O up/O the/O Second/O Amendment/O ./O 
Now/O ,/O it/O 's/O very/O interesting/O ./O 
Today/O I/O heard/O it/O ./O 
Through/O stupidity/O ,/O in/O a/O very/O ,/O very/O hard/O core/O prison/O ,/O interestingly/O named/O Clinton/PERSON ,/O two/O vicious/O murderers/O ,/O two/O vicious/O people/O escaped/O ,/O and/O nobody/O knows/O where/O they/O are/O ./O 
And/O a/O woman/O was/O on/O television/O this/O morning/O ,/O and/O she/O said/O ,/O ``/O You/O know/O ,/O Mr./O Trump/PERSON ,/O ''/O and/O she/O was/O telling/O other/O people/O ,/O and/O I/O actually/O called/O her/O ,/O and/O she/O said/O ,/O ``/O You/O know/O ,/O Mr./O Trump/PERSON ,/O I/O always/O was/O against/O guns/O ./O 
I/O did/O n't/O want/O guns/O ./O 
And/O now/O since/O this/O happened/O ''/O --/O it/O 's/O up/O in/O the/O prison/O area/O --/O ``/O my/O husband/O and/O I/O are/O finally/O in/O agreement/O ,/O because/O he/O wanted/O the/O guns/O ./O 
We/O now/O have/O a/O gun/O on/O every/O table/O ./O 
We/O 're/O ready/O to/O start/O shooting/O ./O ''/O 
I/O said/O ,/O ``/O Very/O interesting/O ./O ''/O 
So/O protect/O the/O Second/O Amendment/O ./O 
End/O --/O end/O Common/O Core/O ./O 
Common/O Core/O should/O --/O it/O is/O a/O disaster/O ./O 
Bush/PERSON is/O totally/O in/O favor/O of/O Common/ORGANIZATION Core/ORGANIZATION ./O 
I/O do/O n't/O see/O how/O he/O can/O possibly/O get/O the/O nomination/O ./O 
He/O 's/O weak/O on/O immigration/O ./O 
He/O 's/O in/O favor/O of/O Common/ORGANIZATION Core/ORGANIZATION ./O 
How/O the/O hell/O can/O you/O vote/O for/O this/O guy/O ?/O 
You/O just/O ca/O n't/O do/O it/O ./O 
We/O have/O to/O end/O --/O education/O has/O to/O be/O local/O ./O 
Rebuild/O the/O country/O 's/O infrastructure/O ./O 
Nobody/O can/O do/O that/O like/O me/O ./O 
Believe/O me/O ./O 
It/O will/O be/O done/O on/O time/O ,/O on/O budget/O ,/O way/O below/O cost/O ,/O way/O below/O what/O anyone/O ever/O thought/O ./O 
I/O look/O at/O the/O roads/O being/O built/O all/O over/O the/O country/O ,/O and/O I/O say/O I/O can/O build/O those/O things/O for/O one-third/O ./O 
What/O they/O do/O is/O unbelievable/O ,/O how/O bad/O ./O 
You/O know/O ,/O we/O 're/O building/O on/O Pennsylvania/LOCATION Avenue/LOCATION ,/O the/O Old/ORGANIZATION Post/ORGANIZATION Office/ORGANIZATION ,/O we/O 're/O converting/O it/O into/O one/O of/O the/O world/O 's/O great/O hotels/O ./O 
It/O 's/O gon/O na/O be/O the/O best/O hotel/O in/O Washington/LOCATION ,/O D.C./LOCATION ./O 
We/O got/O it/O from/O the/O General/ORGANIZATION Services/ORGANIZATION Administration/ORGANIZATION in/O Washington/LOCATION ./O 
The/O Obama/PERSON administration/O ./O 
We/O got/O it/O ./O 
It/O was/O the/O most/O highly/O sought/O after/O --/O or/O one/O of/O them/O ,/O but/O I/O think/O the/O most/O highly/O sought/O after/O project/O in/O the/O history/O of/O General/ORGANIZATION Services/ORGANIZATION ./O 
We/O got/O it/O ./O 
People/O were/O shocked/O ,/O Trump/PERSON got/O it/O ./O 
Well/O ,/O I/O got/O it/O for/O two/O reasons/O ./O 
Number/O one/O ,/O we/O 're/O really/O good/O ./O 
Number/O two/O ,/O we/O had/O a/O really/O good/O plan/O ./O 
And/O I/O 'll/O add/O in/O the/O third/O ,/O we/O had/O a/O great/O financial/O statement/O ./O 
Because/O the/O General/ORGANIZATION Services/ORGANIZATION ,/O who/O are/O terrific/O people/O ,/O by/O the/O way/O ,/O and/O talented/O people/O ,/O they/O wanted/O to/O do/O a/O great/O job/O ./O 
And/O they/O wanted/O to/O make/O sure/O it/O got/O built/O ./O 
So/O we/O have/O to/O rebuild/O our/O infrastructure/O ,/O our/O bridges/O ,/O our/O roadways/O ,/O our/O airports/O ./O 
You/O come/O into/O La/LOCATION Guardia/LOCATION Airport/LOCATION ,/O it/O 's/O like/O we/O 're/O in/O a/O third/O world/O country/O ./O 
You/O look/O at/O the/O patches/O and/O the/O 40-year-old/O floor/O ./O 
They/O throw/O down/O asphalt/O ,/O and/O they/O throw/O ./O 
You/O look/O at/O these/O airports/O ,/O we/O are/O like/O a/O third/O world/O country/O ./O 
And/O I/O come/O in/O from/O China/LOCATION and/O I/O come/O in/O from/O Qatar/LOCATION and/O I/O come/O in/O from/O different/O places/O ,/O and/O they/O have/O the/O most/O incredible/O airports/O in/O the/O world/O ./O 
You/O come/O to/O back/O to/O this/O country/O and/O you/O have/O LAX/O ,/O disaster/O ./O 
You/O have/O all/O of/O these/O disastrous/O airports/O ./O 
We/O have/O to/O rebuild/O our/O infrastructure/O ./O 
Save/O Medicare/O ,/O Medicaid/ORGANIZATION and/O Social/ORGANIZATION Security/ORGANIZATION without/O cuts/O ./O 
Have/O to/O do/O it/O ./O 
Get/O rid/O of/O the/O fraud/O ./O 
Get/O rid/O of/O the/O waste/O and/O abuse/O ,/O but/O save/O it/O ./O 
People/O have/O been/O paying/O it/O for/O years/O ./O 
And/O now/O many/O of/O these/O candidates/O want/O to/O cut/O it/O ./O 
You/O save/O it/O by/O making/O the/O United/LOCATION States/LOCATION ,/O by/O making/O us/O rich/O again/O ,/O by/O taking/O back/O all/O of/O the/O money/O that/O 's/O being/O lost/O ./O 
Renegotiate/O our/O foreign/O trade/O deals/O ./O 
Reduce/O our/O $/O 18/O trillion/O in/O debt/O ,/O because/O ,/O believe/O me/O ,/O we/O 're/O in/O a/O bubble/O ./O 
We/O have/O artificially/O low/O interest/O rates/O ./O 
We/O have/O a/O stock/O market/O that/O ,/O frankly/O ,/O has/O been/O good/O to/O me/O ,/O but/O I/O still/O hate/O to/O see/O what/O 's/O happening/O ./O 
We/O have/O a/O stock/O market/O that/O is/O so/O bloated/O ./O 
Be/O careful/O of/O a/O bubble/O because/O what/O you/O 've/O seen/O in/O the/O past/O might/O be/O small/O potatoes/O compared/O to/O what/O happens/O ./O 
So/O be/O very/O ,/O very/O careful/O ./O 
And/O strengthen/O our/O military/O and/O take/O care/O of/O our/O vets/O ./O 
So/O ,/O so/O important/O ./O 
Sadly/O ,/O the/O American/O dream/O is/O dead/O ./O 
Bring/O it/O back/O ./O 
But/O if/O I/O get/O elected/O president/O I/O will/O bring/O it/O back/O bigger/O and/O better/O and/O stronger/O than/O ever/O before/O ,/O and/O we/O will/O make/O America/LOCATION great/O again/O ./O 
Thank/O you/O ./O 
Thank/O you/O very/O much/O ./O 
We/O 're/O doing/O really/O well/O ./O 
Iowa/LOCATION 's/O been/O amazing/O ./O 
It/O 's/O been/O amazing/O ./O 
We/O 're/O doing/O so/O well/O and/O I/O love/O this/O place/O and/O I/O 'm/O back/O here/O all/O the/O time/O and/O I/O 'm/O going/O to/O be/O here/O a/O lot/O in/O January/O ./O 
You/O 're/O going/O to/O be/O so/O sick/O of/O me/O ./O 
You/O 'll/O probably/O say/O ,/O ``/O We/O ca/O n't/O give/O --/O the/O caucus/O ,/O just/O forget/O it/O ./O 
We/O ca/O n't/O stand/O the/O guy/O any/O more/O ./O ''/O 
No/O ,/O you/O 're/O going/O to/O like/O me/O and/O we/O 're/O going/O to/O be/O back/O and/O we/O 're/O going/O to/O do/O a/O great/O job/O for/O you/O ./O 
Most/O importantly/O ,/O we/O 're/O going/O to/O get/O to/O that/O office/O and/O we/O 're/O going/O to/O do/O the/O right/O thing/O ./O 
We/O 're/O going/O to/O do/O the/O right/O thing/O ./O 
So/O ,/O a/O few/O things/O ./O 
A/O lot/O --/O so/O much/O has/O happened/O ./O 
You/O know/O ,/O when/O we/O first/O came/O out/O ,/O we/O were/O all/O talking/O together/O ./O 
And/O we/O were/O talking/O border/O security/O ,/O which/O we/O 're/O just/O doing/O so/O great/O with/O the/O border/O security/O ./O 
We/O 're/O going/O to/O build/O a/O wall/O ./O 
Mexico/LOCATION 's/O going/O to/O pay/O for/O the/O wall/O ./O 
We/O all/O know/O that/O ./O 
But/O we/O 're/O going/O to/O have/O security/O ./O 
And/O the/O drugs/O are/O going/O to/O stop/O and/O the/O people/O that/O are/O going/O to/O come/O into/O the/O country/O but/O they/O 're/O going/O to/O come/O into/O the/O country/O they/O 're/O going/O to/O be/O legal/O ,/O they/O 're/O coming/O in/O legally/O ,/O and/O that/O 's/O the/O way/O ./O 
That/O 's/O the/O way/O ./O 
And/O it/O affects/O Iowa/LOCATION so/O much/O ./O 
Believe/O me/O ,/O I/O can/O take/O care/O of/O China/LOCATION in/O my/O back/O pocket/O ./O 
That/O 's/O easy/O for/O me/O ./O 
That/O 's/O what/O I/O do/O ./O 
And/O we/O have/O all/O the/O cards/O ./O 
A/O lot/O of/O people/O do/O n't/O know/O ./O 
You/O know/O ,/O these/O politicians/O they/O do/O n't/O understand/O we/O have/O the/O cards/O ./O 
You/O know/O ,/O with/O China/LOCATION ,/O our/O people/O pay/O tax/O ./O 
They/O pay/O no/O tax/O ./O 
It/O 's/O not/O supposed/O to/O be/O that/O way/O ./O 
They/O call/O it/O a/O tariff/O because/O it/O sounds/O better/O ./O 
But/O we/O 'll/O take/O care/O of/O that/O ./O 
We/O 'll/O take/O care/O of/O all/O of/O that/O ./O 
What/O happened/O is/O with/O Paris/LOCATION ,/O there/O 's/O a/O different/O mindset/O ./O 
And/O when/O the/O polls/O came/O out/O last/O week/O ,/O my/O numbers/O went/O way/O up/O because/O people/O felt/O more/O secure/O with/O me/O ./O 
Now/O ,/O maybe/O it/O had/O to/O do/O --/O who/O knows/O why/O ?/O 
Who/O knows/O ?/O 
But/O my/O poll/O numbers/O went/O up/O ./O 
And/O do/O you/O ever/O notice/O whenever/O there/O 's/O something/O that/O I/O do/O that/O 's/O proper/O but/O controversial/O ,/O they/O 'd/O say/O ``/O Oh/O ,/O now/O he/O 's/O gone/O ./O 
That/O 's/O it/O ./O 
That/O 's/O the/O end/O ./O ''/O 
I/O wo/O n't/O go/O over/O all/O of/O the/O different/O things/O because/O maybe/O you/O 'll/O change/O your/O minds/O ./O 
But/O they/O 'd/O say/O ,/O ``/O That/O 's/O it/O ./O 
It/O 's/O over/O ./O ''/O 
And/O then/O they/O 'd/O come/O in/O ,/O ``/O Sir/O ,/O your/O poll/O number/O went/O up/O 9/O points/O this/O week/O ./O ''/O 
I/O said/O ,/O ``/O They/O did/O ?/O ''/O 
Because/O I/O have/O to/O do/O what/O 's/O right/O ./O 
I/O have/O to/O do/O what/O 's/O right/O ./O 
And/O you/O know/O what/O ?/O 
If/O I/O do/O n't/O make/O it/O ,/O I/O do/O n't/O make/O it/O ./O 
I/O have/O a/O good/O life/O ./O 
We/O all/O hopefully/O have/O a/O good/O life/O ./O 
I/O have/O a/O great/O family/O ,/O nice/O people/O ,/O wonderful/O people/O ./O 
They/O love/O me/O ./O 
I/O think/O ./O 
I/O hope/O ./O 
I/O think/O ./O 
But/O I/O have/O a/O great/O family/O and/O I/O built/O a/O great/O business/O ./O 
.../O There/O 's/O such/O spirit/O .../O There/O 's/O such/O spirit/O no/O matter/O where/O I/O go/O ./O 
You/O know/O ,/O I/O go/O to/O Dallas/LOCATION ./O 
We/O have/O 20,000/O ./O 
35,000/O people/O in/O Mobile/LOCATION ,/O Alabama/LOCATION ./O 
20,000/O people/O in/O Oklahoma/LOCATION ./O 
Wherever/O we/O go/O in/O Iowa/LOCATION ,/O we/O have/O these/O crowds/O ./O 
You/O know/O this/O is/O supposed/O to/O be/O .../O for/O like/O a/O record/O ./O 
It/O is/O big/O and/O yet/O it/O feels/O intimate/O ./O 
It/O feels/O good/O .../O .../O So/O I/O changed/O a/O couple/O of/O weeks/O ago/O ./O 
When/O I/O saw/O Paris/LOCATION I/O changed/O ./O 
And/O a/O big/O ,/O big/O part/O of/O what/O I/O 'm/O doing/O now/O is/O safety/O and/O security/O and/O smartness/O and/O smartness/O ./O 
Sort/O of/O interesting/O ./O 
You/O know/O ,/O the/O slogan/O is/O ``/O Make/O America/O Great/O Again/O ''/O and/O I/O 'm/O adding/O ``/O Make/O America/O Great/O Again/O and/O Safe/O Again/O ''/O because/O we/O do/O n't/O feel/O safe/O anymore/O ./O 
And/O the/O problem/O we/O have/O now/O that/O we/O 've/O never/O had/O to/O this/O extent/O is/O the/O power/O of/O weaponry/O ./O 
It/O 's/O the/O power/O ./O 
It/O 's/O the/O tremendous/O power/O ./O 
You/O know/O ,/O 100/O years/O ago/O ,/O I/O would/O have/O said/O ``/O Let/O 's/O not/O go/O ./O ''/O 
I/O said/O ``/O Do/O n't/O go/O there/O ''/O anyway/O ./O 
And/O I/O said/O it/O strongly/O ``/O Do/O n't/O go/O ./O 
You/O 're/O going/O to/O destabilize/O the/O Middle/LOCATION East/LOCATION ./O ''/O 
But/O the/O fact/O is/O right/O now/O ,/O we/O 're/O going/O to/O have/O to/O do/O things/O because/O we/O have/O some/O really/O ,/O really/O sick/O degenerates/O ./O 
And/O the/O press/O --/O look/O at/O all/O those/O cameras/O going/O all/O live/O ,/O all/O --/O you/O know/O ,/O nobody/O else/O has/O cameras/O like/O this/O ./O 
They/O can/O make/O a/O speech/O 100/O times/O they/O make/O a/O speech/O ,/O nobody/O cares/O ./O 
Look/O at/O this/O ./O 
And/O do/O n't/O worry/O ,/O they/O never/O pan/O the/O crowd/O ./O 
You/O know/O ,/O they/O never/O ;/O they/O have/O me/O ./O 
That/O 's/O why/O I/O 'm/O walking/O around/O ./O 
I/O figured/O I/O 'll/O walk/O around/O maybe/O they/O 'll/O get/O the/O crowd/O ./O 
They/O never/O pan/O the/O crowd/O ./O 
I/O tell/O them/O ``/O Pan/O the/O crowd/O ''/O ,/O they/O never/O do/O ./O 
.../O I/O had/O a/O crowd/O 7,000/O people/O last/O week/O ./O 
More/O ./O 
7,000/O people/O and/O in/O a/O confined/O space/O ./O 
They/O had/O 3,000/O people/O outside/O that/O could/O n't/O get/O in/O ./O 
My/O wife/O says/O ,/O ``/O Darling/O ,/O the/O speech/O was/O excellent/O ./O 
Did/O you/O have/O many/O people/O there/O ?/O ''/O 
I/O said/O ``/O What/O ?/O ''/O 
She/O said/O ,/O ``/O Well/O ,/O they/O never/O leave/O your/O face/O ./O ''/O 
They/O keep/O it/O purposely/O ./O 
